Barkin', scratchin',
frisbee-catchin', presidential pets
That's us!
Change into the canines who
drive souped-up cars and jets
Comin' through!
Tuchus-nippin', toilet-sippin',
Soarin' through the sky
I like it!
Lickin', droolin', quick-refuelin'
who said dogs can't fly
Not me!
Speedin', crashin',
villain-smashin' vehicles explode
Ooh!
Chasing, racing down the road
Road Rovers!
Hunter is a hero
hound, leader of the pack
Huh, cool!
Colleen comes from London
town, watch her feet attack
Exile's from Siberia
with super-frozen sight
That's me
Blitz to chews on posteriors,
his bark's worse than his bite
I'm perfect.
Shag is strong from head to
toe, a coward through and through
Muzzle's stack is gonna
blow, he's short a screw or two
They fight for right both day
and night in every episode
Let's roll!
Now it's time to hit the road
Road Rovers!
Scout.
Good evening, Professor Shepherd.
Give me back my dog, General.
Certainly.
Just as soon as the
prototype is loaded
and you've handed
over the blueprints.
Well done.
All secured, General.
Thank you, Groomer.
It's been a pleasure.
Your dog has a very
devoted master.
Enjoy.
I'm here, Scout.
I'm here.
Professor, it seems
you've been had.
Alright, Fluffy, alright.
Go chase some
rabbits, but don't go far.
It's almost supper time.
Yep, right on time.
Supper's all ready.
I'm coming, Fluffy, I'm coming.
Fluffy?
You've gotten into something.
It has begun.
Exile, you have been chosen.
Colleen, you have been chosen.
Shag
You have been chosen.
Yes, you.
Now come.
Shag, now!
Good.
Oh, nice dog!
Blitz, you have been chosen.
Well, these are the last two to go.
Oh.
Finally got word to put
the crazy one down, huh?
Yeah.
Say good night, muzzle.
Same for the mutt.
His time's up.
He's been here six weeks.
No, it's not time
to play, fella.
Come on.
Hey knock it off you two,
let's get this over with.
Hey!
Should I go after him?
Yeah but let's get
rid of this guy first.
Hunter, you have been chosen.
Leave, Hunter. Save
yourself while you still can.
The time has come my pets
The transdogmafier will
change your pure canine forms
into a new species
called Canosapiens.
This is how we say in
Siberia, totally neato.
Oh, look at me.
I'm so handsome
I could kiss myself.
In fact, I think I will.
Mwah.
Well, I'm not crazy
about the color,
but I abso-bloomin'-lutely love the boots.
I would not have predicted this.
No way.
Greetings, Road Rovers.
Greetings, master.
Welcome to Road
Rover Mission Control.
Today you'll be sent
on a vital mission.
Yes, sir!
But first, I want you to greet
the members of your pack.
Yes, sir!
Well, hi.
Hello.
Nice to smell you.
Nice to meet you too.
Hi there.
（dogs greetings）
Perhaps I should have considered cats.
You have all been chosen
for your special skills.
Hunter for his super speed.
You're out!
Blitz the Doberman
for his powerful jaws.
Colleen the collie for
her cunning and agility.
Hello there pretty dog girl.
Oh, dreadfully sorry.
Exile, the husky, for
his strength and vision.
I can see you.
And Shag, the sheepdog,
for his incredible bravery.
Well, I got four out of
five right, so sue me.
Aw, poor fella.
He hasn't become
very human, has he?
Hey, don't sweat it, Shag.
Muzzle hasn't
become human at all.
Aw, isn't that right, Muzzle?
Yeah you crazy aren't you!
Yeah okay bye-bye!
Buddy of mine!
Coooool!
Don't you have the
most interesting friends?
I know!
I'm just lucky that way!
Road Rovers, here's
your first assignment.
Yesterday in Camden, Maine,
a cocker spaniel turned into this!
A few hours later in the same town,
this is what happened to a Dalmatian.
Wow, who's cleaning
up after them?
I would find great enjoyment
biting them on the tushies.
Don't be a weird boy.
This morning, those two
commandeered a freight train carrying
An experimental gene-splicing device
called the molecular stabilizer.
In the wrong hands,
this could be a dangerous weapon
these monsters must be stopped
So Rovers, do you understand your mission?
Yes sir!
Do you realize you will face great danger?
Do you realize that some of you
may not return alive
Ehh, come again?
Some of you may perish
Perish?
Whoa as..as..in perish?
Uh, check please!
I definitely should have
considered cats
Rovers, report to the launch area!
But wait a minute!
If we're putting our lives on the line
What's in it for us?
For your services, I will give
you each three meals a day,
a weekly bath, and a carpet
by the fire where you can sleep.
Do we have a deal?
Hey!
A carpet by the fire.
Change it to a sofa.
You will stay off the sofa!
Okay, okay, off the sofa,
yeah, the carpet is fine, alright.
And if you succeed, I will do my
best to find each of you a home.
It's a deal!
We're off!
Exile, Blitz, Shag,
take the Sky Rover.
You betcha, comrade.
Come on, mop boy.
Colleen, we'll take
the Street Rover.
Roger, Hunter.
Muzzle, you hold down the fort.
Hey, don't worry
pal, we'll be back.
Uh, you know how
to fly this thing?
Not a clue.
Me neither.
Oh boy, this is
going to be fun-ski.
Right, all buckled up.
Then let's hit the road, Rovers.
Hey, what gives?
It's not moving.
You, eh, have to turn
the ignition key.
Oh, right.
Duh. hehe.
Let's hit the road, Rovers.
I should have Scotchgarded the seat covers.
Yippee ki-yo-ki-yap!
So, how do you like my driving?
Let me put it this way.
I hope the airbags work.
Aw, thanks.
That's nice.
Hello, what have we here?
Too cool!
Don't be snow-poking
Exile, schnell faster!
Боже мой!(My god!)
Everybody's always rushing me.
April-day, April-day!
We're going down!
Don't you mean Mayday?
May, June, July, who cares?
We're in deep doggo donuts!
Wow, you two look
much bigger on TV.
Blimey!
Oh, super.
The airbags do work.
I know you're out there.
I know you created
these monsters.
I know it's you, Parvo.
I understand dogs.
I understand their qualities,
their strength, their loyalty.
Canine loyalty.
Control that, and you
can control the world.
It's ready, General.
Good.
Let 'er rip.
It took me a solid year to get
this cano-mutator into operation.
Beautiful
But unreliable.
Get rid of him. Bah!
I need that molecular
stabilizer to make the effect last.
Then I'll create an
entire army of soldiers,
Cano-mutants, powerful, vicious
and above all,
permanently loyal to me.
Soon, all will call me master.
Groomer, what's the good word?
The train is coming, General.
At last.
And there's a slight problem.
What?
No.
This can't be.
More Cano-sapiens.
Only one other person knew
the technology and he's long gone.
Or is he?
Aiya! Akita!
Drop it! Shih Tzu!
Heel!
Rin! Tin! Tin! Stand up!
Roll over! Play dead!
Ai-yah-yah-yah!
Was the "Ai-yah-yah-yah" part from Karate?
No, from Benihana's.
Let the biting begin.
We have the box with that
molecular gizmo, master.
Good dogs
yeah but our friends here aren't
too happy about it.
What do you want us to do?
Listen carefully
I am too young to die
and far too pretty
Freeze!
I love being Road Rover.
I didn't know you could do that
Me neither. must have
contracted it during cold war
You are both lucky stiffies
I did not bite you repeatedly.
I was just joking with you
Put him down!
This is what you want.
No Hunter! Don't give it to 'em!
Give it to them.
Give it to them
I don't think we have a choice
Shag!
We've let the master down
Not really
Hello
If we have the
molecular stabilizer
What'd you give them?
A little present for their leader.
Oh, it's ours at last.
Now my cano-mutants will rule.
Parvo, every dog has it's day.
I'm having one of those
funny deja vu feelings.
To the power of the pack!
They think they've won, but
from the ashes I will rise again!
Ah! I'm glad I went with dogs after all.
You've done well, Rovers.
You're good, good dogs.
You'll be called again to serve.
But until then, enjoy your new
homes as the pets of world leaders.
Exile in Russia,
Colleen in England,
Shag in Switzerland,
Blitz in Germany,
and Hunter in the White House.
But always remember,
that deep inside every dog
is a Road Rover.
Now, as for you
How'd you like to stay here with me?
Keep me company.
You would? That's great.
Welcome home. Scout.
Welcome home.