Barkin', scratchin',
frisbee-catchin', presidential pets
That's us!
Change into the canines who
drive souped-up cars and jets
Comin' through!
Tuchus-nippin', toilet-sippin',
Soarin' through the sky
I like it!
Lickin', droolin', quick-refuelin'
who said dogs can't fly
Not me!
Speedin', crashin',
villain-smashin' vehicles explode
Ooh!
Chasing, racing down the road
Road Rovers!
Hunter is a hero
hound, leader of the pack
Huh, cool!
Colleen comes from London
town, watch her feet attack
Exile's from Siberia
with super-frozen sight
That's me
Blitz to chews on posteriors,
his bark's worse than his bite
I'm perfect.
Shag is strong from head to
toe, a coward through and through
Muzzle's stack is gonna
blow, he's short a screw or two
They fight for right both day
and night in every episode
Let's roll!
Now it's time to hit the road
Road Rovers!
Let's get this stuff out fast!
Where did you come from?
Mayday!
We're taking on water!
Mr. President, it's General
Mills from the Pentagon.
Yes, General.
No.
When?
Hunter, it's time, boy.
Yes!
I love that machine!
Eat up, muzzle.
Want some more?
There's a good boy!
Hey Colleen, Muzzle,
how's is waggin'?
Don't know if that's
any of your business.
Hey, what you got
in the bowl, Exile?
Shag has done it again.
Yet another
culinary masterpiece.
That dog is a gourmet genius.
Shag, another awesome meal, pal.
What's your secret?
Oh, you don't say.
Huh.
So what's his secret?
He cooks everything in toilet water.
Next time, let's get takeout.
Road Rovers, listen while I
brief you on the mission at hand.
Last night in the South Pacific
A U.S. destroyer was struck
by a torpedo and sunk.
Thankfully, there were no casualties.
But the Navy's top secret decoder that controls
an important defense satellite was stolen.
and an unidentified submarine
was spotted leaving the scene.
Rovers, you must track down the thieves.
I am ready, master, to chew
on secret-stealing buttoxes.
Don't be a weird boy.
The fate of the free world
hangs in the balance.
Retrieve that decoder.
Honored to lead the way, sir.
I'm 50% retriever, you know.
And 100% mutt.
I'm not taking orders
from some mixed breed.
I should be top dog.
I have super claws, super teeth.
What does Hunter have?
What are your super powers, huh?
Let me see.
I'm super playful, super
loyal, super trusting,
and super, super friendly.
Can I sniff you?
No.
Well, OK, but that's part of what
being super friendly is all about.
OK, these are the stupidest
super powers I ever heard of.
Now go away.
Of course I'm super fast, too.
Oh, yeah, I forgot.
That's better.
Sorry.
That's OK.
I'm also super forgiving.
We're dogs with a mission.
We are Road Rovers.
Out.
Well, it can't hurt to ask.
Master, can Muzzle come along?
He hasn't been out of
headquarters for a while.
Do you think that's wise?
No way.
That dog is crazy.
A loose cannon,
a total hot head.
Don't get him started, Blitz.
I'm telling you now,
he's unpredictable.
He's totally reckless.
An uncontrollable
force of nature!
Aw, now you're gonna hurt his feelings.
There, there,
that's okay, Muzzle.
Bad doberman saying
mean wordies, yeah.
Take it easy, pal.
Maybe you can
come along next time.
Shag, you come
with Exile and me.
Colleen and Blitz,
take the subber over.
We will have enjoyable
trip together, yeah?
Umm right, and your name is?
Let's hit the road, Rovers!
See you there Colleen!
Cheerio Hunter!
The enemy in sight Colleen?
Affirmative hunter
we have an active ping
Bogey sub on sonar 10 knots ahead
We should overtake it in no time
Oh he's beautiful
Oh, Babushka!
Get load of those two.
What are you guys looking at?
Forest tree Illustrated.
The giant redwood issue.
Yeah.
Ahh.
You two definitely need a hobby.
Okay, so when do I get
a chance at the controls?
Oh, sorry.
I didn't see you sitting there.
I'm Colleen.
Have we met?
Of course.
You know me.
I'm Blitz.
Blitz, Blitz, no, no,
that's not working for me.
I know, I'll give you
a brand new name.
Something that better suits
your winning personality.
Yes, from now on, let's
call you Mr. Fluffy Pants.
Let's not.
Mr. Stoffington Fluffy
Pants, or Fluffy for short.
Stop calling me
that or I'll bite you.
Oh yeah?
With whose dentures, Fluffy?
Jacques Cousteau!
Sachi-mi!
Chav!
Ooh!
Blitz, come in.
Everything
okey-dokey down there?
Just call me Fluffy.
Don't be a weird boy.
Bogey sub heading into port.
Stay with it, Colleen.
We'll make a quick recon of
the island, then be right back.
Exile, what do you see?
To our right side is
gently smoking volcano.
To our left side is
moonlit tropical beach.
And to our front side is enemy
helichoppers coming straight at us!
Huh.
I would not have predicted this.
Fly faster, Hunter!
Fly like a...fly like a...really
fast thing that flies...fast!
Wow, Exile.
You have a way with words.
Thank you, it is gift.
Hit him with the
anti-aircraft lasers!
You betski!
Shaq, get ready!
Take aim!
No, Shag!
Turn it around!
The other way!
Fire!
See?
This is precisely the reason they
don't normally give bazookas to dogs.
Brilliant.
What's the prognosis, Exile?
I'll have Cloud Rover fixed in
two shakes of a Lamb's Jiffy.
What's a Lamb's Jiffy?
Don't ask.
What is it, Shag?
You're kidding me.
What'd he say?
He says he prefers dry
dog food over canned.
Oh, something else?
What?
There goes that bogey
sub with the stolen decoder.
And those choppers are
heading into the volcano too.
Good work, Shag.
Now all we have to do is
figure a way to get inside.
I'll get in.
Blitz, quit rushing!
Let the fighting begin.
Oh, that smells
springtime fresh.
Well, he got in alright.
Yep, he's a dog of his word.
And our job here is done.
No, stay Colleen, stay.
Okay, here's the plan.
I'll keep the guards busy.
You three sneak in.
Ooh, tricky.
Awo!
How does Hunter
do that fire thing?
I don't know?
I just hope it has nothing
to do with his digestive tract.
Let's check it out.
What was that?
I hope we can find Blitz.
Ooh?
The Doberman?
Oh, ugh, right.
He may be pushy,
but he seems brave.
Please let me go.
You were saying?
So they sent in a dog to do a man's job
or rather they sent in a Road Rover
Actually I'm not a Road Rover.
I borrowed this suit
for a costume party.
Really.
I don't even like dogs.
They're too drooly honest
Please let me go
We better go get him
before he sells out his mother
Oh, I'd love to, Hunter, really.
But we've run into a bit of a sticky wicked or what.
Oh, hi!
You must be sticky.
Or are you wicked?
I always get you two confused.
This steel is harder
than KGB's heart.
I want to go now.
Look on the bright side, guys.
The Road Rovers are
back together again.
Welcome.
I am Captain Zachary Storm
And you the Road Rovers,
are about to witness
the total destruction of
the United States.
Let the fun begin.
I know what you're
thinking, Rovers.
Yet another megalomaniac
on a volcanic island planning
global conquest.
Yeah, exactly.
It's been dull.
Boring.
The difference is, dogs, I
have the firepower to do it.
You see, I hold here the only decoder that controls
the Navy's top secret satellite of mass destruction.
And you're just in
time to see it in action.
In a short while
when the satellite is
in the proper alignment,
I'll fire the lasers
obliterating 10 key US cities.
And do you know why?
Yeah, because you're mad at the NFL for
letting the Cleveland Browns move to Baltimore.
Besides that...
Because you're a member
of the night of the month club
No! Don't you treat me like
the others did back in the gulf
Just because I opened
fire without a direct order
I was court-martialed
They gave me a dishonorable discharge
Big mistake, now I discharge this!
But first let me bid my
canine friends a fond farewell.
Bye-bye.
Yet another unexpected twist.
Bummer!
Captain, the city
coordinates are locked in.
And everything is
ready for departure, sir?
It better be!
What was that?
All systems are go, sir.
The satellite will be
in place in 60 seconds.
Hang in there, Exile!
I'm trying, but I'm in
big time need of Visine.
No!
Hello?
What is that?
We are free!
And here's our rescuer now.
Muzzle, where'd you
come from you crazy nut?
We cannot hold them
for long comrades.
Let's save our own
necks while we still can.
No, we have a
mission to complete.
We have to stop Storm.
But how, Hunter?
We have no weapons!
We need something unpredictable.
Something totally reckless.
An uncontrollable
force of nature.
Hey!
We need Muzzle!
Now!
All right, buddy.
Muzzle off!
Oh Muzzle take it easy! Eww!
Okay, that's enough for me.
Me also
'Tis much worse than Chernobyl.
Go, Muzzle, go!
Make sour platin' out of them!
Ah!
Now that is sick.
To the power of the pack!
Nice work, comrade.
I've got the decoder.
So much for Storm's big plans.
Hey, where is that
crackpot anyway?
Fortunately, dogs
don't have nine lives.
They have just one, which is
about to end for the Road Rovers.
Colleen and Blitz,
take the Ocean Rover.
Wait, where's Musk?
Oh no.
Where are you going?
Mussel's my pal,
I gotta save him!
You'll never make it!
Hey, I have no choice!
Why?
It's one of my
powers, I'm super loyal!
Exile, what do you see?
I'm afraid my comrades are lost.
Well, Mussel, I don't know which of
my superpowers can save us this time.
Oh yeah, I almost forgot that one!
I'm super, super lucky!
Let's take it home Rovers!
Master, it would have been
the end of the road for us.
If old muzzle here
hadn't hopped to the rescue.
So next time Blitz, maybe
we don't have argument
over whether muzzle comes or not.
Yeah yeah okay I'm sorry.
I made a small mistake
about the little muzzle dog
and about hunter too
Yeah, yeah, all right.
I guess you're not such
a stinky leader after all.
Hey, that's nice.
Thanks.
That was eloquently put.
Dankeschon, pretty lady.
You're welcome, Fluffy.
I'm thinking of changing my name
But I like Fluffy.
You've done well, Rovers.
You're good, good dogs.
As for the decoder, we'll
need to return that to the Navy.
I know, Master,
and we will, too.
Just as soon as Captain Storm
is picked up by the authorities.
Shaq, can you keep that
bad guy busy till then?
Woof woof!
No, stop!
I...I surrender!
Really! I give up!
Just stop! Jesus please
Stop!