Barkin', scratchin',
frisbee-catchin', presidential pets
That's us!
Change into the canines who
drive souped-up cars and jets
Comin' through!
Tuchus-nippin', toilet-sippin',
Soarin' through the sky
I like it!
Lickin', droolin', quick-refuelin'
who said dogs can't fly
Not me!
Speedin', crashin',
villain-smashin' vehicles explode
Ooh!
Chasing, racing down the road
Road Rovers!
Hunter is a hero
hound, leader of the pack
Huh, cool!
Colleen comes from London
town, watch her feet attack
Exile's from Siberia
with super-frozen sight
That's me
Blitz to chews on posteriors,
his bark's worse than his bite
I'm perfect.
Shag is strong from head to
toe, a coward through and through
Muzzle's stack is gonna
blow, he's short a screw or two
They fight for right both day
and night in every episode
Let's roll!
Now it's time to hit the road
Road Rovers!
Now Charles, let's
run through this again.
I get the country home.
Yes, Dime.
And the cars, including
the Bentley and the Rolls.
Yes, Dime.
And the Diamond Tiara.
Ah, what a charming dog.
Here, boy. Here.
And over here is Big Ol' Ben.
Whoo-ee! Hehe
That's a big clock. Haha
Bet you take some humongous
batteries and quadruple E.
You know what?
It takes a lick and
it keeps on tickin'!
Hey! You scat-dogs!
You're ruining my home video!
Wait a second, ZZ!
Bad dogs! Bad bad dogs!
Road Rovers let's roll!
It's time for the
gnashing of tushies!
Don't be a weird boy.
Colleen, I am close relative to wolf.
Let me talk to them
in their native tongue.
Be my guest, Exile.
Yeah, definitely not from
around these neighbors.
Maybe they're French!
You are the worst driver in the world.
If you don't mind, I'd like
you to meet my boyfriend.
We're going steady.
Maybe they'd like to play a game of catch!
I don't get it!
What are you gonna do with that?
Ah, well I get it.
You wanna try one?
Eh, maybe later,
in my next lifetime.
Cool, call me.
You can do this, Shad!
You just need courage,
you need strength!
And most of all, you need our
brand new Road Rover missile launcher!
It is fun!
Shag, we definitely gotta get you
a refresher course on the launcher.
Hi-ya Ma-donna!
Eww, gross!
Blimey!
Do you know how much trouble I
go through every day to look this way?
Ta-ta! Don't bother to write!
Wow, Exile, when did
you learn how to do that?
I'm called Siberian Knights.
It comes in handy.
Oh, that bungle tuckered
me bones a bit, now.
Yeah, what she said.
I am feeling not so hot myself.
Let's head home, Rovers.
Our job here is done.
This is troubling, Rovers.
First the reports of
those roaming wolf packs,
then the disappearance
of the royal family,
and now this.
Does this hurt?
Нет (No)
Arrgh да(yes)! да(yes)!
I found out what hurts!
We also found this.
Must be from those
wolves with lips that foam!
Might be.
We should get it tested.
Right.
We'll run it through the
world's most advanced,
state-of-the-art DNA analyzer.
Where did you find this, Hunter?
It's something we picked up
in London, Professor Hubert.
Can you get a fix on it?
Certainly, my boy.
I'm a bloodhound.
Possessing the world's
most sensitive canine nose.
And you've had garlic.
Huh?
With anchovies.
So will your analysis take long?
To do this right, I'll need
to compare this sample
to the scent of every
creature on the planet.
I'll have the results
for you by morning.
Aardvark? No.
Alligator? No.
Anaconda?
No.
The morning of June 11th, 2870.
Ah Blitz, you are so handsome.
I could look at you all night,
you big hunk of dog muscle, you.
You know, I'm so pretty I could
kiss myself all over, which I will.
Because I can!
Hey, what are you doing here?
This isn't working, mop boy.
Mommmy!
Baboon? No.
How are the lab
tests going, professor?
Good news, I'm
already on the Bs.
Badger?
No.
Bandicoot? No.
Bandicoot, cool.
What's the problem, buddy?
You had a dream you were
shaved bald by Kathie Lee Gifford?
Worse than that?
Oh, you saw a werewolf!
Wake up and go back to sleep, you big nut.
No! I saw it too! It was big,
ugly and huge with dripping fangs and...
But I wasn't scared, no, not one bit.
You're both acting like little babies.
Okay, who got
into the chocolates?
Whoever it was
went into Exile's room.
Yo, Exile.
Wake up, buddy. Move it!
Quit rushing me.
I suppose this is your werewolf?
Who, me?
Blimey, could you
blokes keep it down?
I need my bloomin' beauty sleep.
I'll say!
Uh-huh-huh.
There's your comedy.
Sorry, Colleen, but
the boys here think
we've gotten uninvited
guests in the house.
Well, if you see them,
tell them to pipe down.
I'm going back to bed.
Yeah, me too.
I've had enough of
these shaggy dog stories.
Me three.
Don't be again unsleeping.
Mother Russia.
It couldn't be me.
Or could it?
Rise and shine, Rovers! Breakfast time!
Walrus? No.
Whale? No.
Wolf?
Yes!
Interesting, very interesting
The testing is complete
Good job professor!
Nothing to it, Hunter
I do have the most sensitive nasal
detection system in the world you know
and you sir are currently in the
possession of a footlong hot dog
with mustard relish and onions
You wouldn't happen to
have an extra one would you?
Ah thanks
So professor, what'd
you find out about the fur?
Although it appears to be from a wolf,
Closer analysis proves it
originates in fact from
A werewolf
I would not have predicted this.
See? I told you it was a werewolf.
And it went straight into Exile's room.
Blimey!
Where is Exile anyway?
Exile?
Go away!
Hey, we gotta talk, buddy.
Leave me lonely.
I do not wish to hurt comrades.
We want to help you, man.
Just tell us what you know.
According to legend of my ancestors,
once victim is beaten or
scratched during full moon,
He turns into a raging monstrous beast!
Sounds like a fun date.
It's нет(no) fun-ski.
It is me, it is Curse of Werewolf.
Oh, I miss Mother Russia.
Father Russia I don't miss much.
He was big grump.
But mother Russia I miss.
Listen to the sad strains of the Baralaika.
I hate it so...
Somebody shut that thing up!
Tonight there is another full moon
Lock me up and throw away key!
No Exile we're gonna help you
But how? How do we find the cure?
We need to consult the great
wise dog of the mountain.
Confuseus!
Ol' Confuseus we seek your wisdom
Did you bring the cocktail weenies?
Yes sir!
Ah! Oh, the Cheezee kind!
Good! Just leave the box!
Yeah, the entire box!
What can I do for you?
Please tell us, ol' great wise dog!
How to save our friend
from the werewolf's curse.
Werewolves curse!
Right! Got it!
Pardon me
The victim's problem
will have ceased
when you find the
drool of the beast
Add water from the English moor,
And you will have the perfect cure.
But if you fail by the dawn of day...
Forever a werewolf, he will stay!
That's it! Get out!
Let's get that swamp water
Rovers. It's back to England.
Thanks, Confuseus
My pleasure! Good luck!
Wear seat-belts!
And next time, pick some sourball.
[freestyle]
Okay, Shag and Exile
will go with me.
And I will go with Colleen.
Have we met?
I'm Blitz. Remember?
Sorry, governor.
I need a name tag.
Let's hit the road, Rovers!
Next stop, the English moors.
You should have left
me behind, Hunter.
Any minute I could change.
Nah. Honestly, Exile, we had
the situation all wrapped up.
And not a moment too soon.
Full moon off the right wing.
How do you feel, buddy?
Hot.
Sweaty.
Large.
The way I always feel.
Sky Rover to Cloud
Rover, I've got good news.
Exile is not a werewolf.
I've got bad news!
Colleen is.
Yet another unexpected twist.
Bummer.
Colleen! It's me!
The one you can't remember! Blitz!
Can't we discuss this over a cappuccino?
Okay guys, here's all
the swamp water we need.
Hunter, we have a problem!
Yeah, I know. We ran out of milk bones.
That's not what I'm talking about!
Stay Blitz, now that we
have the swamp water
we've gotta find
some werewolf slobber.
I got plenty of that!
Where are you going now, Blitz?
It's not up to me!
Colleen's in charge!
What are they all doing here?
According to the legend
of my homeland
It is time for werewolves to
pick their king and queen.
Once sun comes up and night turns to day.
They will all be
werewolves forever.
Queen Colleen?
Nah, no way!
Yoo-hoo over here!
Hunter, let's get out of
here while we're still dogs.
I barely got away by the skin of my teeth.
Play dead, Blitz.
We're not going
anywhere without Colleen.
Okay, Rovers Let's roll!
Finally, it is time for the
biting of soft mushy parts.
Don't be a weird boy.
I love being Road Rover!
Colleen, he's not really your type,
in fact, he's not even your species.
Shag, you gotta turn it around!
You did it, Shag! Good work!
You know, I'm
usually super-patient
but with the sun coming up,
I just don't have the time.
Just a touch of
swamp water and...
Catch!
Ew! Gross!
Gooey! But it did the job!
Here, you want
one for a souvenir?
Hunter, you're
just too good to me.
Hey, I'm also super generous.
You're good dogs, Rovers.
Good, good dogs.
I'm glad to see that Colleen is
back to her beautiful self, too.
Ah, me too.
She almost took my
tuchus off back there.
And thanks, professor.
Your nose has done it again.
You've had linguine and
clam sauce haven't you?
Well, yes.
And an after dinner mint too.
Amazing.
And you've been chewing
on a slime covered tennis ball.
Hey, I'm a dog.
Some habits die hard.
All is well!
And you've had cocktail weenies.