Barkin', scratchin',
frisbee-catchin', presidential pets
That's us!
Change into the canines who
drive souped-up cars and jets
Comin' through!
Tuchus-nippin', toilet-sippin',
Soarin' through the sky
I like it!
Lickin', droolin', quick-refuelin'
who said dogs can't fly
Not me!
Speedin', crashin',
villain-smashin' vehicles explode
Ooh!
Chasing, racing down the road
Road Rovers!
Hunter is a hero
hound, leader of the pack
Huh, cool!
Colleen comes from London
town, watch her feet attack
Exile's from Siberia
with super-frozen sight
That's me
Blitz to chews on posteriors,
his bark's worse than his bite
I'm perfect.
Shag is strong from head to
toe, a coward through and through
Muzzle's stack is gonna
blow, he's short a screw or two
They fight for right both day
and night in every episode
Let's roll!
Now it's time to hit the road
Road Rovers!
Centuries ago, the
nations of Katzenstok
and Eisneria lived side by side
in peaceful coexistence.
Their friendship was
epitomized by
the golden bridge that
linked the two countries.
But then came war.
The two nations collapsed,
as did their golden bridge.
And the peace was washed away
apparently forever.
The only surviving remnant
of these ancient days is..
The priceless Scepter of the Valley,
long enshrined in
Katzenstok's capital.
But the Scepter has been...
Stolen!
Stolen by spies from Eisneria!
That's a lie!
We stole nothing!
My people resent the accusation!
If Eisneria does not return
the Scepter by noon tomorrow,
Katzenstok will have no
choice but to declare war!
War, then war it will be!
The ambassador from the
United States has the floor!
The US wishes to assure the
General Assembly that as we speak,
some of our finest operatives
are looking for the missing scepter.
Hang ten, Moondoggie!
Wrong sport, Aren't it?
Oh, then why is there surf music?
I hope he's in a good HMO.
Don't you kiss me!
I will not!
I will kill you!
Don't do that either.
Here's our ride!
Just in time!
Start rushing, comrades!
They are right behind you!
Let's hit the road, shag!
Oops.
The EPA's not gonna like this.
You're just a wealth of
commentary today, aren't you?
Just trying to stay topical.
You know, ripped out
of the day's headlines.
Rear of Tank Rover
also ripped out.
Okay everybody, back up nice and easy.
One more step and...
Strap yourselves in!
Now!
We're home free, Rovers.
I would not have predicted this.
Your predictions are consistently off.
Oh, you know this!
Put it this way, the
psychic hotline you're not.
Hold onto your hat!
Jingle balls, jingle
balls, jingle all the balls
What?
Jingle bells?
Never heard of them.
This is making me see red!
They'll be singing
soprano into their 80s.
Good.
We Russians love the opera.
Hey, Blitz.
How you doing there, Muzzle?
You been here long?
Yeah.
My tootsie-wootsies
are all frost-bitten.
How'd it go?
Like taking candy from a baby.
Very angry baby.
Let's roll, Rovers.
But what about the
biting of the enemy?
Not now, Blitz.
We have what we came for.
And if we don't give this sparkly
back to Katzenstok by noon tomorrow,
we'll have a real
bloomin' war on our hands.
I love it when you talk to me.
Have we been introduced?
Sure, you know me.
Oh, right.
Your name is...
No, no, don't say it.
Let me think.
Blister?
No.
Blighter.
Blitz.
No, no, no.
That's not it.
Bloaty?
Oh, I definitely
want one of those!
Cool!
Me too!
I'd also like a parachute.
Anything we can do?
Yeah, get ready to crash!
Any other suggestions?
Yeah, I suggest we all
scream uncontrollably!
Sounds like a plan.
It's a little late to start
writing your memoir, Shag.
Before we die, I just want
you to know that I love you.
Please consider therapy.
Huh?
Actually, Hunter, that was
one of your better landings.
Hey, thanks.
That's sweet.
Hey, Exile, radio mission control.
We need someone to come get us.
No can do, Hunter.
Radio, she kaputski.
Ohh, here's someone
coming to get us right now!
They went into the village
Surround the perimeter,
and search every building.
They're around here somewhere.
Oh, brilliant.
The place is
crawling with rebels.
We'll lay low till nightfall.
We can sneak out once it's dark.
Till then, here Shag,
Guard this with your life.
Okay, guard it with
Blitz's life, but guard it.
Hey, no way, mop boy.
Alright alright,
guard it with my life!
His argument was very
persuasive you know.
Blinky!
No that's not it,
don't tell me, I'll get it.
I'm starting to hate this a bit.
Madam Ambassador,
it's the Pentagon.
What's the outlook General?
Well, we just lost radio
contact with the Rovers.
Oh no.
Afraid so.
We believe they were shot
down north of Katzenstok
and Eisneria, in the
region of Ovitznia.
We've sent in some planes for
reconnaissance, but so far no sign of them.
Isn't Ovitznia controlled
by rebel guerrillas?
That's affirmative.
They're a lethal group
led by a real troublemaker by
the name of Colonel Gustav Havoc.
Idiots.
Now let me get this straight.
We steal the Scepter of the Valley
in order to throw Katzenstok
and Eisneria into war.
And then the scepter is taken
from us by a pack of dogs?
They were talking dogs, sir.
I don't care if they
were singing dogs!
I don't care if they were
singing the theme from Cats!
I want that scepter!
Yes, sir!
We have the Rovers surrounded
in the village of Moosk.
They'll never get away.
I swear on my life.
I'll hold you to that
promise, Lieutenant.
Colonel Havoc, the Katzenstoki
Prime Minister is still waiting on line 2.
Stanislav, sorry.
The phone keeps ringing.
What's the good word?
I've arranged the financing.
24 billion.
Wonderful!
Once the funds show up
in my Swiss bank account,
the missile launchers will be
delivered to you within 24 hours.
Ciao!
The Eisnerian
ambassador is on line 4.
Alonzo, baby, I've
heard the news.
What can I do to help?
That's why I've called.
We need your military support.
Well, sure, Lonzi,
but it'll cost you.
Our treasury is
at your disposal.
Good.
Let me crunch some numbers
with my money people.
I'll get right back to you.
I love war.
Whose side are you on, Colonel?
My side.
I'll sell to whomever
pays my price.
And after I clean
out their treasuries,
I can sit back and watch
Katzenstok and Eisneria
blow each other to bits.
After which, I'll sweep in,
pick up the pieces, and lead.
Lieutenant
Colonel
Shoot anything that moves.
Just get me back that scepter.
Yes, sir.
Steady, Janni.
It's only a wolf.
Sometimes they come down
the mountain looking for food.
Ah, it was just a wolf.
I swear I saw them.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Poor fella.
He's been shot.
Easy now.
Here's a goodie for ya.
Someone get the first aid kit.
This kid needs help, and fast.
I want every building flattened.
Demolish the place!
Why, Lieutenant?
We'll flush them out.
Move it!
Antiseptic.
Cotton.
Suture.
Clamp.
There.
All done.
Nice work, Exile.
My pleasure.
May I faint now?
Be my guest.
Thank you.
Alright everybody,
we're running late.
Grab a quick bite to eat
and get ready to move out.
There you go, muzzle.
Hey, Blitz, you want a biscuit?
Tanks.
You're welcome.
No, tanks.!
Are you sure?
It's tasty. Try it.
Tanks!
You're welcome.
No, tanks!
What's with you?
You want it or not?
Tanks!
You're welcome.
No! Tanks!
Well, make up your mind!
Oh, ho-ho-ho, tanks!
Now I get it.
Funny.
Ach du Lieber! Run!
Let's hit the road, Rovers.
Hunter, do everything!
Turn, turn, turn!
Hey, The Byrds did that tune,
Exile. I love that song.
Turrrrnn!
Colleen, I think
that one was Janis Joplin.
No shag we're not
making a pit-stop now
Hey, see what you can
get on the radio, Exile.
This is Road Rovers
calling Mission Control.
Come in, Mission Control.
Oh, I was thinking of some
music, but that's cool, too.
Aah!
Everybody out!
Yet another unexpected twist.
Bummer!
We've located the
Rovers, Colonel Havoc.
I'm not blind.
I can see that, Lieutenant.
Hand over the scepter, dogs.
Never, Havoc.
I'm afraid you really
have no choice.
Can't we all just get along?
Give it to me now.
I would have it but I'm afraid my
friends wouldn't be very pleased.
Huh?
Awaiting orders, Colonel.
Just get in the chopper
and get us out of here.
Good news Mission Control.
We found the Rovers,
and they have the scepter.
Thanks for our help?
Thanks for yours, mate.
Cry "Havoc!" and let slip the dogs of war
Uh, yeah, what he said.
Jolly good job, Blintz.
Uh, close enough.
To the power of the pack!
And so, war was averted
between Katzenstok and Eisneria.
And to celebrate their renewed friendship
Katzenstok returned
the Scepter of the Valley
to its original place of honor
where it had rested years ago.
To our future of friendship.
The nations were once
again united in peace.
And the region became known
as the happiest place on earth.
Thanks to the Road Rovers.
You're good, good dogs.