Seven dog years ago, the laboratory of
geneticist William Shepherd was destroyed.
And his research
stolen by terrorists.
Shepherd survived the
attack and went underground
to create a new breed of super
canines who fight for justice.
These dogs are the pets of world leaders,
but when called to action, they become
a team of awesome crime fighters.
They're known as
the Road Rovers.
Barkin', scratchin',
frisbee-catchin', presidential pets
That's us!
Change into the canines who
drive souped-up cars and jets
Comin' through!
Tuchus-nippin', toilet-sippin',
Soarin' through the sky
I like it!
Lickin', droolin', quick-refuelin'
who said dogs can't fly
Not me!
Speedin', crashin',
villain-smashin' vehicles explode
Ooh!
Chasing, racing down the road
Road Rovers!
Hunter is a hero
hound, leader of the pack
Huh, cool!
Colleen comes from London
town, watch her feet attack
Exile's from Siberia
with super-frozen sight
That's me
Blitz to chews on posteriors,
his bark's worse than his bite
I'm perfect.
Shag is strong from head to
toe, a coward through and through
Muzzle's stack is gonna
blow, he's short a screw or two
They fight for right both day
and night in every episode
Let's roll!
Now it's time to hit the road
Road Rovers!
Anything?
Nah, it's just
another quiet night.
Hold it right there!
This is bad news.
Road Rovers, a new brand
of evil has reared its ugly head.
Aw man, I like the old brand.
Actually, the new brand
of evil has more nuts.
Mmm, yummy!
We have confirmed four museum break-ins
around the world in the past 24 hours
The perpetrators are...
guys in pajamas!
No, ninjas.
Cool!
All of the missing artifacts
once belonged to the most
powerful samurai of ancient Japan
the Kurikawa
The ninjas have already
stolen four Kurakawa remains.
A banner, a disc of jade,
a teapot and a china vase.
The only other Kurakawa object
the statue of Buddha, remains
inside a temple in Japan.
So what's the plan?
Go to Japan, Rovers,
and stop those ninjas!
Yes, Sir!
Let's hit the road, Rovers!
The Sonic Rover is the
fastest jet ever made.
How come you get to fly it?
I have a license.
A pilot license?
No, a dog license.
I do not understand this
book called Go Dog Go.
Why does the boy dog not
like the hat of the girl dog?
It seems like
perfectly fine hat.
Well, you've got to read
the whole thing, Exile.
Oh, there is payoff.
Ah, I will read that.
Aw, Shag, you were
supposed to go before we left.
Okay, hold it till we find a
Ming vase inside the museum.
Exile, you and Blitz go around
and check out the rear entrance.
Excellent. I bite anything
that comes out of the rear.
Sigmund Freud would have
field day with nut boy like you.
I know it's closed, Shag, but we're
not coming back in the morning.
Remind me never to
get on Colleen's bad side.
Abso-bloomin'-lutely fantastic!
Cool statue!
Ah, I am disappointed.
No ninja tushies to bite.
You're one strange, funky dog man.
Hey, cheer up, Blitz.
It looks like we beat
those ninjas to the punch.
Can you guys teach
me how to do that?
Comrade, I am believing that
is Japanese for "big fat нет"
Give 'em the cold shoulder, Exile!
I love being Road Rover!
Maybe I'd better stick
to making snow cones.
Sick 'em, Blitz!
I would, really I would.
But I'm feeling a little fluish.
My tushie biting bouquet when
you care enough to send the very best
See mop boy,
Nothing to be afraid of
Yes, I actually liked Stallone
in Judge Dredd. I really did.
Excuse me, fella. Care to dance?
No way they're gonna
get their hands on you.
I saw it first!
I lost it!
I would not have predicted this.
As you say in America, this is stinky.
So is the ninja's scent.
They're not wearing any deodorant.
And they smell like dogs.
The scent leads into this cave.
What do you mean we
need to go back home?
I'm sure you didn't leave a
pot roast in the oven, Shag.
And I turned off the coffee.
Blitz is missing.
Oh, Exile.
That's the nicest thing
you've ever said to me.
Ha ha ha.
I say it again if you like.
You-hoo!
Hi, pretty lady.
Need a lift?
No, thanks.
My mum taught me never
to take a ride from strangers.
I'm stranger?
Stranger than anyone I know.
We're off.
Smells like those
ninjas split up.
We better do the same.
Roger.
Who is Roger?
There we go.
Comfy.
Much better.
Okay, Shag, it's
just you and me now.
So stay close.
Whoa, not that close.
I think they headed this way.
Whose wheels are those?
That smell is strong here.
No, not you, buddy.
The ninja's.
Большая!
Uh, comrade Colleen, perhaps
you should Go Dog, Go!
Relax, Exile. I really don't
need a backseat driver.
If you do not speed up
soon, there will be no backseat!
Mommmmy!
Blimey!
I've seen some rude drivers in
my time, but this one takes the cake!
He is also licking our frosting.
You are disgusting me.
Push another button
before the hurting start
Good shooting.
Thanks, Exile. Aye, aye, please.
Excuse me, but don't
be forgetting about me!
Who?
Ugh, that stuff smells worse than
your Limburger tuna melt, Shag.
Okay, okay, it's almost as bad.
Hey, nice fit pal.
So do you have the final piece?
I am grateful for your efforts.
It's Parvo.
Yet another unexpected twist.
Bummer.
You shall be properly rewarded.
Yes, we will let you live.
I smelled the dogs, but I should
have smelled the rat, huh Shag?
Shag? Oh no!
General, I've scanned
the first four artifacts.
With this final element,
we will have our map.
Proceed.
It's coming together!
Yes, we've got it.
Lock the coordinates now!
What is this?
Shag! Let him go!
Shepherd's pets can't leave their
running noses out of my business.
Too bad, Rovers.
This is going to be
your last mission.
Lozenge!
Activate the suction pumps.
Yes General.
Excellent lozenge, by the way.
This is no time for
whimpering, Shag.
Shag. This is the time for whimpering.
Take these two Road Rovers
to the Cano-mutator.
And have them reconditioned.
We'll pass on the reconditioning.
Just a shampoo and
rinse will be fine, thanks.
It's on the run!
Looks like skipping to me.
Follow it but don't get too close.
She's led us straight to the nest.
The hole's too small for us to get in!
Not for long.
Perfect!
The nest is mine.
What should we do about the mother?
- Blast her.
- But why?
I don't need her.
I need the eggs.
Aye, sir!
No!
I should have driven.
This tunnel got us nowhere.
That is not true.
We got this out to the open.
Got fresh air, we can stretch our legs.
And we can see the wildlife up close!
Blimey!
Maybe this is just a bad dream.
Yeah, that's it, Blitz.
Just one too many Spielberg movies.
Just keep telling yourself, there's no
place like home. There's no place like home.
I need ruby slippers.
You need analysis.
This is the last time
we leave Muzzle behind.
Now, Shag!
Ah, back to the pound for those two.
You know, Shag, it's really
too bad Muzzle missed this.
He would've loved the exercise.
There is nothing like the
power of a newborn baby's love.
Oh, my little ones.
Once your kind ruled the earth,
and now with me as your father,
we will rule it again.
Soon, you will grow
to love and obey me.
Oh, yes.
We'll be one big happy family,
loyal to each other
and hungry for conquest.
And they say nobody cares
about family values anymore.
Some say, let sleeping dogs lie.
But I say, wake up
and smell the bacon.
Shag, I'll go after Parvo.
Watch this little guy.
I'm counting on you, pal.
General, I have failed.
What do you mean?
I told you to
blast the dinosaur.
I tried.
This is a disappointment.
Let's stand and fight!
Discretion is the better part of valor.
What does that mean?
It means let's get out of here!
Lozenge!
Okay kids, it's back home for you.
Yoo-hoo! Hunter!
What's with the eggie waggies,
Huntie-Wuntie?
Later, Colleen. Right now we've got to
get that green mist back into the cave.
That's what keeps these dinosaurs asleep.
How do you know that?
I spied on parvo.
We can do it with that gizmo.
Easy as cake, like taking pie from a baby.
Yeah, what he said.
Ooh, better hurry, guys.
Mama's not a happy camper.
Yo, Shag!
Aw, I love family reunions!
Sleep well, kids!
See you in a few thousand years!
To the power of the pack!
Don't worry, love.
You and all the shiba inus
will be returned to your masters.
Exile, why are you crying?
I have finished my book and I am
deeply moved by the joyous conclusion.
It turns out the boy dog like the
hat of the girl dog very, very much.
Aren't happy endings cool?
I love happy endings!
We love you, too.
You've done it again, Road
Rovers, you're good, good dogs.
You may each have a doggy treat.
Let me get this straight.
We saved the world,
and a doggy biscuit is a thanks
we get for a job well done?
That's about the size of it.
I love this gig!