Barkin', scratchin',
frisbee-catchin', presidential pets
That's us!
Change into the canines who
drive souped-up cars and jets
Comin' through!
Tuchus-nippin', toilet-sippin',
Soarin' through the sky
I like it!
Lickin', droolin', quick-refuelin'
who said dogs can't fly
Not me!
Speedin', crashin',
villain-smashin' vehicles explode
Ooh!
Chasing, racing down the road
Road Rovers!
Hunter is a hero
hound, leader of the pack
Huh, cool!
Colleen comes from London
town, watch her feet attack
Exile's from Siberia
with super-frozen sight
That's me
Blitz to chews on posteriors,
his bark's worse than his bite
I'm perfect.
Shag is strong from head to
toe, a coward through and through
Muzzle's stack is gonna
blow, he's short a screw or two
They fight for right both day
and night in every episode
Let's roll!
Now it's time to hit the road
Road Rovers!
Yeah, we got the mutts.
We're ready to move.
It's okay, sport.
It's okay.
You're going home.
Hey, what do you
think you're doing?
This is my dog.
You're mistaken, ma'am.
No, you are.
This dog was stolen.
And I'll bet the
others were, too.
I'm making sure
you get shut down.
The only thing that's
shuttin' is your yap.
Proceed with the prosecution.
Thank you, Your Honor.
Ladies and
gentlemen of the jury,
We will prove beyond
a shadow of a doubt
that Donovan Bell is responsible
for the disappearance
of Olivia Perrou.
Mr. Bell! Please, Mr. Bell!
Mr. Bell! Are the
accusations are true?
What did you do with Perrou?
Is it true you're the head of a
nationwide dog-napping operation?
With outfits in every major city.
What does this dog-napping weigh?
Ha ha ha!
The Feds got nothing on me.
There's no case.
This isn't funny, Donovan.
You've got some serious
time hanging over your head.
Listen up, John Law.
There was only one witness.
A dog.
And dogs can't talk.
You wanna bet on that?
Try reading the papers sometime.
I want that dog.
There he is!
Gotcha!
The man will be pleased.
Let's fetch him, Road Rovers!
Coming through!
Huh?
Nooooooo!
You can rest easy, cub.
Soon as we heard you needed a witness
protection program, we were on the way.
Hey, you're a celebrity, man.
Can I get your autograph?
Schnell Hunter, these biker
boys are bad humans.
Bad, bad humans.
Faster Huntie-Wuntie
Oh, Colleen, don't call me that.
It's insubordination.
You'll demoralize the troops.
Oh, I want to have elation kisses!
There!
Now, that's more like it!
I love being Easy Rider!
I am born to be wild dog man!
Don't worry Shag
next time you can try.
I like you, too, Shag-ster.
But I am also fond of my spleen!
Hey you! Oh baby baby baby!
I'll be biting you soon!
Blitz, put a leash on it,
will ya? We're in uniform.
Oh, right. Sorry.
Fluffy pants.
Let me give you a hand.
I just had the manicure.
Hunter, have you gone daffy?
You're driving us
straight into the ocean.
AHHH! You're right!
We're gonna drown!
Help!
AHHHHH!
Just kidding, bro.
You are messing with
my head, puppy boy.
To the power of the pack!
Translation?
Sport says he saw everything.
The bad guy's hideout,
the sale of kidnapped dog,
And the fight between his
master and that gangster.
He's the perfect
witness, Rovers.
We need him to testify
at the trial in Miami.
But how, Master?
He's just a little doggy.
Deep inside, every
dog is a road rover.
You mean...
Precisely.
Come on, boy.
Into the trans-dogmafier.
No, it's okay, buddy.
It doesn't hurt a bit.
Look at me.
Hey, I've got a uniform.
Pants are a little big, but I
can always have them taken in.
Hey, I can talk too!
And I've got a lot to
say, believe you me!
You know, I'm gonna
like being a Road Rover.
Welcome to club
comrade Sportovich.
I give you big kiss.
I give all my comrades big kiss.
Stop with the kissing
or I'll start with the biting.
Okay, I give you
big bear hug instead.
No, go back to the kissing.
Go back to the kissing.
Kiss me, kiss me!
Don't be weird, boy.
Do they do this often?
Oh, not often
enough, in my opinion.
We're off to the courthouse
in Miami, Rovers.
They're waiting
for sport to testify.
Hey, is there any
food on this flight?
I'm starving.
What, no beverage?
Now, that's more like it.
So how fast does this baby go?
Like the speed of light?
Uh, the Turbo Jet Rover is
fast, but it doesn't do miracles.
That is too bad.
We could use one right now.
You know, all of a sudden,
I don't think I want to be a
Road Rover anymore.
Let's see.
The odds of us getting away
from these blokes scot-free,
calculating all factors,
are one in 3,007.
That bad, huh?
Doomed.
How's it wagging, guys?
Sheesh, they couldn't hit
the broadside of a hydrant.
So let me get this straight.
You guys are going
to protect me, right?
Calm down, scaredy dog.
No one will touch you.
I will bite that tushies first.
You'd do that for me?
He'd do it for anyone.
Buckle up, crew.
We're gonna to be
experiencing a little turbulence.
Check this out, guys.
Make it stop, please.
Make it stop.
I'm feeling the tiniest
little bit squeamish!
Ta-da!
Impressive!
But can you do this?
Woah!
Can you teach me to do that?
Nah, you gotta be born with it.
Lucky dog.
Okay, pal, you can shoot at me,
but you can't shoot at my friends.
I take it back, Sky Jockey.
You can't shoot at me either.
Too bad for you.
Pretty nice view.
Hey, this is a
one seater, buddy.
Bad move.
You don't know a whole lot
about gravity, do you, pal?
Shag, you are definitely
a dog's best friend.
Oh please, oh please, oh please.
If you let me live,
I promise I'll go back to
obedience school for a solid year.
I promise.
I love being Road Rover.
Cars turn into boats,
planes turn into subs.
Eat that, bad guys.
Okay, about the
obedience school thing.
Okay, maybe not a whole year,
maybe more like once a month.
Okay, okay, a whole year.
Sheesh, what a grub!
Good news, we've lost him.
And Florida is straight ahead.
What's getting my
Billy Goat Gruff is,
how do baddest
guys keep finding us?
What's it matter?
You Road Rovers really know
how to shake a dog off your tail.
But of course, we are
professionals, especially me.
I'm number one in shoe chewing,
number one in garbage sniffing.
And of course, no one
can touch my tushy biting.
Please, I have weak stomach.
I smell sunbathing lotion,
senior citizens and white shoes.
We must be in Miami.
So you can relax, Sport.
You're gonna get
your day in court.
Not a pretty picture we've got here, guv.
Parvo
I would nothave predicted this.
Let me go, you witch!
Don't try to sweet-talk me!
Sport, stay!
We'll take care of Parvo!
Боже!
(God!)
Little doggy has lost all his biscuit!
All right, Mr. Parvo.
Sir, I kept my part of the deal.
The Road Rovers are yours.
Sport?
Wow. You're working for Metalhead?
Sorry, it's strictly business.
If I didn't wear this homing device
in my collar and lead you to parvo,
he said I'd never
see my master again!
Yet another unexpected twist.
Bummer.
See?
Canine loyalty is unbeatable.
It always serves me well.
Lozenge!
Yes, General.
So if you let my master go,
we'll be on our way.
Oh, that is so quaint,
in a naive sort of way.
But no, you both know too
much about my operation.
That makes you a security risk.
You know what to do with him.
I've done a bad thing.
I've ruined everything.
And as for Shepherd's pets...
I look forward to seeing
them get cut down to size.
Good idea!
Run!
Listen, I'm not
really a Road Rover.
I was just going along for the
ride, you know, just for the fun of it.
I should be spared, you know?
Nice try.
First we gotta rescue Sport.
That canine is a traitor.
He's shameless.
I can't believe anyone would ever turn
on their friends and be such a wimpy baby.
Oh, I can think of someone.
And he's a weird boy.
Sport was just trying to
save his tail and his master.
Tennis, anyone?
I can't wait to fix
the two of you.
Pardon, I abso-bloomin'-lutely love the
red tights, but that helmet has gotta go.
What did you say?
Hi-yah!
Gu-chi!
What is wrong with you?
Retrieve the prisoners!
I will not fail.
Hop on cutie, I'll take
you away from all this.
Stick with me kid, you won't ever
have to worry about a thing again.
Peachy!
Lozenge!
Shag, what gives?
Cool shell!
Yeah, be perfect
for your collection.
Excuse me Huntie-Wuntie, but
we do have a previous engagement.
Yeah, but the shell
You're amazing, sport!
I never knew you had it in ya!
Me neither, and I love it!
They're in sight, General!
Don't bore me with the
details, just do your job!
Lining up.
What?
Eh, nothing.
Up for a ride through the Everglades?
I hear they're lovely this time of year.
Okay, Shag.
Afterwards, we'll go to GatorWorld
in Orlando and wrestle alligators.
but just the little ones.
Hey, what are friends for!
Have you gotten the fix on them?
Target in sight!
Let's get this over with.
Odd, I just had the brakes checked.
General, I think I found the problem.
We're on ice.
That's not possible.
Freeze-dried swamp lamb.
I like it.
I am not a happy person.
Lozenge!
Honey lemon?
I'd prefer cherry if
you've got it, dear.
Sure, General.
And I was hoping for
such a pleasant day.
Proceed with the witness.
Mr. Sport, can you point
out the person in this room,
responsible for the
kidnapping of Olivia Perrou.
Yes, that's him right there!
Donovan Bell!
Lousy snitch!
Has the jury reached a verdict?
We have, Your Honor.
In the matter of the
people versus Donovan Bell,
we find the
defendant guilty as charged.
To the power of the pack!
That was fun!
What are we gonna do now?
The dognapping operation
is shut down, master.
You're good dogs.
You're good, good dogs.
Of course I am the best.
I knew all along that
Sport couldn't be trusted,
but nobody ever listens to me.
If I was the leader, we'd
never get caught by surprise.
Hey, Sport.
I guess you showed Blitz
it all worked out in the end.