Barkin', scratchin',
frisbee-catchin', presidential pets
That's us!
Change into the canines who
drive souped-up cars and jets
Comin' through!
Tuchus-nippin', toilet-sippin',
Soarin' through the sky
I like it!
Lickin', droolin', quick-refuelin'
who said dogs can't fly
Not me!
Speedin', crashin',
villain-smashin' vehicles explode
Ooh!
Chasing, racing down the road
Road Rovers!
Hunter is a hero
hound, leader of the pack
Huh, cool!
Colleen comes from London
town, watch her feet attack
Exile's from Siberia
with super-frozen sight
That's me
Blitz to chews on posteriors,
his bark's worse than his bite
I'm perfect.
Shag is strong from head to
toe, a coward through and through
Muzzle's stack is gonna
blow, he's short a screw or two
They fight for right both day
and night in every episode
Let's roll!
Now it's time to hit the road
Road Rovers!
Alright.
One, two, three, four, five, where's six?
Let's go!
Get up! Mutt!
I said, get up!
Heel!
Sit!
Halt!
Next time you won't be so lucky.
Let's see...
Too old.
Too scrawny.
Too small.
Cute.
Very cute.
I hate cute.
Oh yes, much better.
You're already near perfection.
Of course, you'll have
to shed a few pounds
but I can help you with that.
There's no need to be frightened.
You've been chosen to be a
member of the new master race
A race of unstoppable cano-mutants.
If you measure up.
Those recruits that lack the
stamina leave in the reject truck.
Huh, it's a one-way trip.
Bye-bye-na!
Hasta mañana!
And did I mention that no one
has ever escaped from here?
Alive.
Reconditioning starts tomorrow morning.
Lock 'em up!
Lozenge?
Yes. Hurry!
How many dogs came in today, Groomer?
Close to 300, General.
The operation is running smoothly.
Ah, yes.
Even my cough is better.
Oh, Parvo.
When I see you
like this, I want to...
give you a quick trim.
Good evening, General Parvo.
Hope you are feeling most pleasant.
Cut the happy chat, Commander.
What's on your mind?
My compatriots and I would
like an update on our investment.
Naturally.
Within the next 24 hours, I will be
shipping out platoons of cano-mutants
to our seven key
locations around the globe.
Once these regiments are in place,
we shall begin the great
attack simultaneously.
And after your government is in place?
As agreed, you will all be rewarded with
high-ranking positions in the new regime.
Until then!
Take a note.
After the takeover, eliminate
the commander and his partners.
Oh, parvo.
Your genius is matched only
by your luxurious facial hair.
Ma petite, come close and whisper
my three favorite words to me.
Complete world domination.
Blimey, I thought you'd
never switch positions,
Got a bloomin' crick in me neck.
Mama lion to pack leader,
mama lion to pack leader!
Do you read me?
Like a book, mama lion.
How are accommodations?
Well, it's no Buckingham Palace.
Big mama, this is king of jungles.
I'll be there soon to rescue
your beautiful cano tush.
Yeah.
Do I know you?
Oh, not this again.
Have you left the nest yet?
We're about to fly the coop.
Here we go, Shag.
No, wait!
Get back!
Slight change of plans, Hunter.
Our wings just got clipped.
Now's our chance!
Shag, we might need to buy you
a tape of Sweatin' to the Oldies.
Nice job, eh? Let's go!
Now, let's see if we can
find a way out of this place
before you kill me.
Mama lion, mama lion. Can you
and baby cub arrange a visit for us?
Just as bloomin' soon as
we can find a way out of here.
Come on, I'll lead the way.
Just for a change, why don't you lead?
He's actually quite a good dancer.
Shag, get your launcher!
Not lawnchair!
Launcher, as in launch.
Not your lunch! Your launcher!
Let me take it from here, Shag.
For me? Thanks!
Excuse me, miss. You need some help?
Well, I could use a
little roadside assistance.
Then again, so could you.
You sure pulled the woolly lamps over
eyes of early worm and got bird in bush.
Okay, cool.
It's not fair.
I wanted to bite his tuchus first.
We're here on business, weird boy.
Not pleasure.
Oh, never mind.
Let's roll, Rovers.
We have two on the inside
and a lot more needing to get out.
Next!
Life is good.
You wanted to talk to me, General?
Yes, Hawkins
There are, some minor details
I need to work out with you
before your first shipment of soldiers.
We have a deal, everything is set right?
We've run into a
few production delays,
due to unexpected
equipment repairs.
I'm afraid it's all quite expensive.
What's it going to cost?
Ten million should handle it.
Of course if you don't want to
be a part of my new world order.
I'll have to confer with my associates.
Do that, but quickly!
I have other offers on the table.
Okay, we need a plan
I know just the one.
I should go in biting.
The puny cano mutant girlie boys
are no match for my marvelous muscles.
Admit it, go on!
Blitz, there are at least 50 of
them and only three of us.
Yeah, one of us should stay
behind to make it a fair fight.
I could be that one!
You are that one
Colleen, what are the odds of
getting through the fence?
According to my calcs, one in 17,002.
Oh, that bad.
We're dead.
Blimey.
You can forget going
over the fence, Hunter.
Only one way is safe.
Going under.
Way, way under.
Okay, Rovers.
Let's hit the dirt.
Good idea, Blitz, but I
had something else in mind.
Wait! You cannot
leave without me!
Where does it say in manual that we can't?
Page 27.
Fine print always confuses me.
Noses up crew, get ready to
hit the surface nice and easy.
Rovers, we're in.
But what do we in?
This is just a guess, but I'd say
we broke into the guard barracks.
Okay, I just remembered I
forgot to bring long underwear.
I'd better go back.
It really gets chilly this time of year,
and I'd hate to freeze my heinie.
So, what's the good work, guys?
That wasn't exactly the
word I was looking for.
So you want to play that game?
Well I have a better one.
Here boy!
Fetch the ball! Fetch!
That's a good dog.
A good, good dog.
There shall be much
wailing and mashing of teeth.
Run puppy girls!
This big bad brother
is out to get you!
Боже мой!(My god!)
These bad mutant doggy men are
always rushing me around all the time.
But can they ice skate?
Come to papa Blitzie!
Comrade, are you dokey okey?
I was trying to stop mutant doggy men.
Argh, Blitz bit me!
Okay, that's it.
You mister need a time out.
As soon as we get
back to headquarters,
you're going straight to
your room, young man.
But he started it with
his icy eyeball thingy.
Well next time I want
you to use your words.
We'll have no more biting around here.
You're singling me out.
Now let's see.
Where are Colleen and Shag?
Move out, Shag.
Ah! Just the dog I was waiting for.
You need to get ready
for the cano-mutator.
But first a slight trim.
Don't make me run with scissors!
That's no way for a
future cano mutant to act!
Stand still...
or there might be an
unfortunate accident.
Lungs are good.
I like that in a dog.
I have to use this more often.
Pack leader to mama lion.
Do you read me?
Loud and clear!
Hey, didn't even hear you!
You're good, Colleen!
I'm glad you noticed.
It's good to see you too, pal.
Say, did you get a haircut?
No, it looks good.
Now that we are in this little
prison camp, how do we get out?
First, we gotta free the dogs.
Which ones?
All of them.
Hunter, are you totally crazy?
There are 10,000 mutts here.
I know, and we're gonna break them out.
Pretty cool, huh?
Freedom for all doggies.
I like it.
The 10 million will be in your
Swiss account in matter of minutes.
I appreciate it commander.
And I hope nothing will hold
up the process any further.
Don't worry commander.
I've taken care of everything
I want a complete
compound lockdown, soldiers!
The shipment of our new platoons
begins in exactly one hour
Is coast clear as seemed?
Okay Rovers. Let's do what dogs do.
Sniff ourselves?
Bite tooshies?
Chase cats?
Roll in garbage?
Bite tooshies?
No, dig!
Oh, yeah, we can do that.
Nice job, Exile.
Now to short circuit the security system.
Hmm... not that one.
Not that one either.
There!
I hate glitches in this system.
Single file, room for everybody.
Women and puppies first.
Oh, especially you, hi.
No shoving please.
Hey, nice fur.
Road Rovers!
I should have known.
Sorry creepy lady but we
don't have time for silly haircuts.
Maybe next time, okay?
No!!!
Just follow Shag.
Blimey! Shag stop!
You drive a hard bargain, General.
But the deal is finally in place.
It's all in your hands now.
That's a good place for it
One by one each country
will fall to me as planned
I have the army, the recruits, the
funds and soon I'll have the world
What, what?
Where, where are the dogs?
How did this happen?
It was the Road Rovers, sir.
But it was your...
responsibility
Lozenge?
No I don't!
I mean yes!
Give me...
Yes.
Broke.
Gum?
All the dogs have been
returned to their homes.
Thanks to you Road Rovers.
You're good dogs.
Good good dogs
What's wrong, Shag? Fleas?
You sure?
Looks like we forgot one