Barkin', scratchin',
frisbee-catchin', presidential pets
That's us!
Change into the canines who
drive souped-up cars and jets
Comin' through!
Tuchus-nippin', toilet-sippin',
Soarin' through the sky
I like it!
Lickin', droolin', quick-refuelin'
who said dogs can't fly
Not me!
Speedin', crashin',
villain-smashin' vehicles explode
Ooh!
Chasing, racing down the road
Road Rovers!
Hunter is a hero
hound, leader of the pack
Huh, cool!
Colleen comes from London
town, watch her feet attack
Exile's from Siberia
with super-frozen sight
That's me
Blitz to chews on posteriors,
his bark's worse than his bite
I'm perfect.
Shag is strong from head to
toe, a coward through and through
Muzzle's stack is gonna
blow, he's short a screw or two
They fight for right both day
and night in every episode
Let's roll!
Now it's time to hit the road
Road Rovers!
Oh, Bast, Sekhmet, Ra, it is time to rise.
Breath in the air, open your eyes!
You mummies wake up!
And as I raise this knife, tell
me the secret of eternal life!
It's working!
What?
Tell me it isn't so!
The late winds of the desert...
No, the mummies are waking!
You must finish the ritual,
so we can live forever!
No!
Let me drive, Colleen.
Please!
Oh, pipe down, Huntie!
It's my turn and you know it.
Look out!
That was close.
It was not that close.
It was close.
Oh, stop it, would you?
What are you looking for?
A map?
No, my donor card.
Coming through!
Uh oh!
Eat fire, Rovers!
Jolly good shot!
Eh, sometimes things just work out.
Where's Shag and Exile anyway?
Uh, they're with Blitz.
Who?
The Doberman.
Oh, wait!
Have I met him yet?
I think...
Here they come
What she saying?
I think he said hello, can
you direct me to Médano?
No!
Follow that van,
They are getting away!
Faster! Faster!
Slower! Slower!
Hit the brake!
Hey!
What are you? Some kind of crazy
psychotic taxi car driving mad man?
He says yes,
you are absolutely correct.
Oh. Hehe.
Fun city.
What kind of a ride was that?
He says an $85 ride.
Plus tip.
Okay, everyone, look alive.
The groomer's scent is strong around here.
Blimey.
Chasing cats.
That is so immature.
But we are dogs.
Yeah, some habits die hard.
Bloomin' mutts.
Hey!
Move it!
Bummer! She's history.
So is Shag.
Where'd he get to?
Shag!
Shag! Where are you Shag?
Oh General!
I told you, I hate cats!
Dogs can be transmutated
and trained, but not cats!
Get rid of them!
But General, they'll make powerful soldiers.
Just look at the claws in this one.
They're smart, strong, agile...
And unpredictable.
You can't control a feline.
Oh yes you can.
Prove it.
Watch.
I've already made a few
adjustments in the cano-mutator,
to accommodate
trans cat mutation.
Magnificent, aren't they?
I find them... disturbing.
Shaq's signal's strong.
He's in that refinery.
You're wasting my time groomer
Oh, nice. See what you've done.
You've led the Rovers straight to me
I should pull your stripes for this!
No problem.
My recruits will take care of them
Soldiers are you ready?
Good, good kitties
Hunter exactly where are we?
I think we're in New Jersey.
Oh, yeah, we're definitely in New Jersey
Yeah, I think it's Piscataway
Ah, very punny!
Little girly cats, go eat kitty litter!
There's only one way these felines could
have been turned into raging monsters.
Parvo.
Two points for the winner.
Bull's eyeball.
Easy as cupcake.
Piece of bean.
Боже мой! (my god!)
My icemaker's on the fritz!
Yes! Cats hate water!
Pathetic!
Shut them up!
Please, General, let me explain.
I've had enough of your
lectures on felo-mutants, Groomer.
Those mutts are on my case,
thanks to your experimental mistakes.
Get rid of them!
No.
What?
I just gave you a direct order, missy.
And I'm not obeying it.
I'm not hearing this.
It sounds like mutiny.
Call it what you want, but I'm leaving.
You're going nowhere!
It's a new day, dear.
Get used to it.
We're coming, Shagster!
No, wait!
What are you doing?
The cano-mutator is mine!
Was, General.
Was.
This isn't happening!
We're through.
No, Groomer!
No!
You can't leave!
Lozenge!
I'm not your nursemaid anymore, General.
You're on your own.
Have a nice life.
Shag's close.
Very close.
Hey, I'm glad to see you alive too, pal.
You still owe me five bucks.
It's not over yet, Groomer.
No one disobeys me.
Good morning, Rovers.
As you know, there's been no
sign of Parvo for over twelve months.
Our operatives from around the
world continue to monitor the situation.
Recently, we have received
some strange reports out of Cairo.
No cano-mutants to speak of,
but giant killer cats have
been spotted near the Sphinx.
Oh, giant killer cats, cool!
They're felo-mutants.
Huh?
Sniff out the trail rovers.
Just be careful out there.
These aren't your normal house cats.
Боже мой! (my god!)
What is that wait?
Wait, I see a sign. It says...
Trespassers will be shot
Well, they weren't lying
We're going down you better bail.
Call me a chiropractor.
You' re a chiropractor.
Thank you!
You... you spoke to me!
Sorry, I'm drawing a blank.
You are…
Scare the bloomin' fur right
off me hide, why don't you!
This is not my cup of tea.
The empress awaits you.
Empress?
You've done well, my pets.
The Groomer!
As you can see, the reports of my
death have been greatly exaggerated.
My kittens and I flew south for the winter
and came across this little fixer-upper.
The Groomer, she has lost case
of baskets needing manly marbles.
Okay, sorta.
Watch the prisoners, I
must prepare for the sacrifice.
Okay, come again.
I'm about to receive
the secret of eternal life.
To succeed there must be a canine offering.
You Road Rovers should fit the bill.
But I'm not really a road rover.
Ask her.
She doesn't even know me.
Oh, I know him.
He's a Road Rover all right.
What?
What are you saying?
Don't be so modest.
You know you're the number one Road Rover.
You say so all the time.
No!
Oh, Bast, Sekhmet, Ra, it is time to rise.
Breathe in the air, open your eyes.
You mummies, wake up!
And as I raise this knife, tell
me the secret of eternal life.
It's working!
Immortality will be mine!
I wouldn't be making any long range plans.
What?!
Good ol' switcheroo-ski!
Pretty cool mummy suits, huh?
No!
The ritual isn't over yet!
Dankeschön.
Thank you, thank you!
Oh, Bast!
Oh, Sekhmet!
Oh, forget it!
I had all.
A cano-mutator, an army of invincible cats,
A city of my own
And immortality it was almost mine!
Now, now I have nothing.
I didn't need her.
I don't need anyone!
I... do miss her sneer.
But... she defied me.
No one ever defies me.
But I...
I really miss her.
General?
Come get me.
Please?
Gr... Groomer?
You've done well, Rovers.
For now, the world won't be going to
Parvo's dogs or the Groomer's cats.
Pretty she-dog.
Now that we're on speaking terms,
why don't you and I take a stroll?
Just the two of us?
Excuse me, but if you'd
like an appointment,
you'll have to call my service.
An appointment?
I bet the schedule is all booked.
General?
Can you ever forgive me?
Look, I saved this for ya!
You disobeyed me!
But you are so against using my cats!
Why?
Why?!
Why!
Eww!
THIS is why!
You're a cat!
I am not an animal!
I'm a man!
But how?
Do I... disgust you that much?
Why no, I actually find it...
appealing.
You do?
Oh, most definitely General.
We're back together.