Barkin', scratchin',
frisbee-catchin', presidential pets
That's us!
Change into the canines who
drive souped-up cars and jets
Comin' through!
Tuchus-nippin', toilet-sippin',
Soarin' through the sky
I like it!
Lickin', droolin', quick-refuelin'
who said dogs can't fly
Not me!
Speedin', crashin',
villain-smashin' vehicles explode
Ooh!
Chasing, racing down the road
Road Rovers!
Hunter is a hero
hound, leader of the pack
Huh, cool!
Colleen comes from London
town, watch her feet attack
Exile's from Siberia
with super-frozen sight
That's me
Blitz to chews on posteriors,
his bark's worse than his bite
I'm perfect.
Shag is strong from head to
toe, a coward through and through
Muzzle's stack is gonna
blow, he's short a screw or two
They fight for right both day
and night in every episode
Let's roll!
Now it's time to hit the road
Road Rovers!
With your speed, you would
make great pizza delivery boy.
I put them in Siberian deep freeze.
I'm tired of playing
with these poppy dogs.
Let the tushie biting begin.
That's enough already.
I wanna to go home.
Let's muzzle them.
That's a good idea.
This is very difficult.
Can you find little bunny
rabbit in this picture?
Ah, good job! That was tough.
Oh..Muzzle
Simply dreadful.
Man, oh man.
I think that's against the law.
Road Rovers
Sometimes we look like little leaguers.
That Rottweiler.
It's a shame your cano-mutants
don't fight with his passion.
Perhaps it's time to
try a different approach.
I love bugs, completely
and unconditionally.
They are my life's work.
And they are my very best friends.
Bugs are survivors.
The mighty dinosaurs
perished from the earth.
Plagues and wars have ravaged
mankind, but bugs have managed to thrive.
Now with the nuclear age come great
dangers in the form of toxic waste.
And our ultimate nightmare,
a global nuclear winter.
Insects will be the only survivors.
If the human race is to continue,
we must not simply study bugs,
we must become bugs!
All of this and more can be
found in my latest book, I BUG
And with the proper funding, I'll
be able to approve my theories.
Professor?
Yes?
Fill in whatever amount you
need to finish your research.
But who...
An anonymous patron
who believes in your work,
and who now has a vested interest.
Enjoying the music, kids?
Heh heh heh.
Isn't Mozart soothing?
Oh! Time for your radiation.
Hmm. Amazing.
That's the biggest
jolt I've ever given you.
You're not getting weaker.
The radiation is actually
making you stronger.
In a nuclear winter, you
would become invincible.
Professor, allow me to introduce you to
your one and only patron, General Parvel.
Well, it was either funding you
or investing in a Broadway show.
But theater people can
be so high maintenance.
I'm honored.
I'm here for a status report, Professor.
Alright, but...
I have some concerns about you making
me change the subjects of my experiments,
from ants, to fleas and ticks.
And I object to these
restricted areas in my lab.
Your lab...?
This is my lab, professor.
I paid for it. Every brick,
every microchip, every bug.
Greta here provided you with
the fleas, ticks, and mange.
And so, your progress?
Well, I won't be finished
with my research for years.
You don't understand.
What do you have for me today, now?
But I'm not finished.
That's what you think.
What is that?
The cano-mutator.
It's used mainly for dogs, but...
I've added some new options
to accommodate your research.
Something I call the bug-hibachi.
Ah, a magnificent flea!
A marvelous, blood-sucking tick!
And the ever-glorious mange.
No!
You've perverted my
research into these monsters!
You're a sick man, Parvo!
Now you're gonna hurt my feelings.
Destroy him.
No! Stop!
Father!
Uh-oh!
I said destroy him!
No one harms father!
Oh, now, now, there's
no cause for violence...
Yet!
Professor, I've funded your dreams
when others wouldn't even listen to you.
Can't we come to some
mutually beneficial arrangement?
Flee, stop!
Let's hear what the man has to say.
Oh yes, yes, uh... Flee.
Let's talk.
Rovers, your services are needed.
An explosion has just struck the T-Bone
dog biscuit factory in upstate New York.
What is shag's problem.
He says this time it's personal.
Find out who is responsible
and bring them to justice.
We're there!
Oh just one last thing before we go master.
What's that?
How do you do that thing with your eyes?
Special effects.
I did not know that.
Let's hit the road, Rovers!
Wait a minute, what's this?
Over here, lads!
This trail is fresh!
And these tracks are a total mystery.
And they head straight to GenPar Inc.
Can you crack the lock, Exile?
Piece of beans, can of cake
Come on already, open it, open it!
Quit rushing me!
Close it, close it!
Well, we can either stand and fight,
- Or...
- Or we can muzzle 'em.
That would be mean, sadistic and cruel.
- Is that a problem?
- Works for me.
Muzzle, here boy! It's playtime!
Okay guys, it's the usual
rules and as always...
No cheating!
Hey, I don't know what
you're talking about.
All my friends in Germany
call me Honest Blitz.
Right, all one of them.
Okay, everybody ante up.
The name of the game is Stud Poker.
On the count of that's what I am, a stud.
That's funny.
I don't hear the familiar
sounds of mass destruction
that always go along with muzzle.
That's odd.
No way!
What is wrong with this picture?
Boy dog meets girl dog.
Isn't romance wonderful?
It's evil Parvo man.
Yet another unexpected twist.
Bummer.
I'm here to see to it,
that all you dogs go to heaven or worse.
You three have a simple job.
Tear apart the Road Rovers.
This... this isn't right.
Sit down, professor, if you want to
keep your funding and your health.
Road Rovers, let's roll!
Admit it, I'm good.
Do I have to?
Maybe not.
Let that acid spewing
thing touch me!
Exile, do something!
These times like this, I
wish I stayed in Siberia.
Why, these bugs are even more
treacherous than I had imagined!
Oh I love it when you laugh!
No, this is not what I intended.
Flea, tick, mange, stop!
Don't harm these creatures!
They are not your enemy!
Yes!
Dog's not true enemy!
Come!
Professor Atwater, this is the
end of a beautiful partnership.
Groomer, let's move out now.
I paid top dollar for those mutants,
and I have no intention of losing them.
The old revolving wall escape trick.
Bummer numero dos.
I'm working on my Spanish.
Ay caramba!
Hey, thanks for calling
off the goon squad, pal.
It's the least I could
do, but you must help me.
Please stop my babies from
harming themselves or others.
Babies?!
You know, I think the professor's
wires are seriously crossed
Heh, you should talk.
Aww, there there Romeo,
there'll be other girl dogs.
Let's hit the road, Rovers!
Oh, look who left a trail!
Flea, tick, and mange.
Oh no.
I think I know where they're heading.
The upstate nuclear power plant.
To be invincible!
Flea will make nuclear winter.
Only insects will survive.
Invincible!
Good luck, and try not
to hurt my little ones.
I'm really not worried about them.
They can take care of themselves.
I'm the fragile one.
You're the weird one.
These boots were made for stomping.
Who's next then?
How's it scratching, buddy?
A little flea joke there.
Ooh, sounds like strep.
The tear gas is loaded.
Target flea and prepare to fire.
No!
Quick! Release Greta, have
her get rid of that mongrel.
I hate to rain on your parade, Muz,
but this is a bad time
for a romantic interlude.
She already has a boyfriend.
Muzzles gonna blow!
Go boy!
Muzzle the ship!
Oh, it sounds awful!
Genau(Exactly)
Once I destroy reactor
core, only insects will survive!
Okay, I gotta stop this big
bug from destroying the world,
but at least I got a cool suit.
I know we've got that whole
dog flea thing happening here.
But what say we give
these a chance, okay?
Farewell, dog!
Adiós, muchacho!(Bye, dude!)
No, flea!
Stand back, professor!
Stop this, flea, right now!
Father!
You will all perish
in a nuclear winter!
There's your nuclear winter.
It's my Siberian deep freeze.
Old Family recipe.
Alright.
Thank you, Exile.
I will never forget this.
I will love you always.
We need long talk.
Get us out of here, Grover!
Aye, sir.
I've just had this ship's detailed, ugh!
One big, happy nuclear family.
Oh, my little misguided ones.
You were trying to help,
but you went about it all wrong.
Now there's an understatement for you.
Well done, Road Rovers.
You're good dogs.
Good, good dogs.
We would have done better if
it wasn't for loud, crazy, Muzzle.
Don't worry, boy.
Find the right girls someday.
Okay, Shag, time to send
them back to their proper home.
They can take away my funding,
and they can take away my lab.
But they can't take away my friends.
And you bugs are my very best friends.
What? You have a plan?
Tell me, tell me everything!
Really?
Oh yes, don't worry.
You can count on me.