Barkin', scratchin',
frisbee-catchin', presidential pets
That's us!
Change into the canines who
drive souped-up cars and jets
Comin' through!
Tuchus-nippin', toilet-sippin',
Soarin' through the sky
I like it!
Lickin', droolin', quick-refuelin'
who said dogs can't fly
Not me!
Speedin', crashin',
villain-smashin' vehicles explode
Ooh!
Chasing, racing down the road
Road Rovers!
Hunter is a hero
hound, leader of the pack
Huh, cool!
Colleen comes from London
town, watch her feet attack
Exile's from Siberia
with super-frozen sight
That's me
Blitz to chews on posteriors,
his bark's worse than his bite
I'm perfect.
Shag is strong from head to
toe, a coward through and through
Muzzle's stack is gonna
blow, he's short a screw or two
They fight for right both day
and night in every episode
Let's roll!
Now it's time to hit the road
Road Rovers!
Hunter's Log, stardate
the day after yesterday.
We've been searching
doggedly for General Parvo.
Bummer.
There's nothing here but empty space.
Looking at X-Ray of Blitz's brain?
Who?
You know. Weird boy.
Okay. Keep it up, Exile.
And the biting of the
mushy parts will begin.
Ew.
Blimey, this is odd.
The sensors indicate that Parvo is close,
but the scanner shows
the field totally clear.
Oh, boy.
It's Parvo.
They never saw us coming, Groomer.
Yes, General.
Those dogs are no
match for your brilliance.
And?
And your strength is
more than theirs combined.
Go on.
And you are more of a
man than they will ever be.
Yes, I am.
Battle stations, Rovers.
Disengaging Rover's saucer.
Begin defensive maneuvers.
Let's lead him astray.
We might have to cancel
our weekend plans, Huntie.
But what about our golf game?
Well, I guess you'll have to
practice your 9 iron on Parvo.
That should tee him off.
We have turbulence.
It's a black hole.
Is that a good thing?
It is if you want to be
compressed into oblivion.
Cool.
Everything's under control, General.
I'll have us out of here as
soon as I set new coordinates.
Right.
First, obliterate those dogs!
But the ship is breaking up!
Don't disappoint me!
Can you get us out of here, lad?
Give me a minute.
We don't have a minute.
Oh, then buckle up, Rovers.
Look, Parvo's ship
It is kaputski!
Oh, that is so sad.
Huh?
I broke a nail.
Oh...
Let's head home, Rovers.
Groomer, we're losing the Rovers!
I'm trying, General!
Don't try. Do it!
I know you're disappointed, General.
But I'll make her up to ya, I promise!
Actually, Groomer.
There's a bright side to all of this.
There is?
This black hole was exactly
what I've been looking for.
If I can harness its power...
I can build a device for
traveling through time.
Why would you want to do that?
You'll see.
Ah, it's great to be home.
Now, time for a little
zap in the cano-mutator!
Oxygen! I need my oxygen!
Oh, you've got to stop these
treatments, General!
I don't think they're helping you.
Nonsense.
It's... making me a better man.
Soon, I'll be rid of my former
feline self.
But that's not first priority now.
The time transporter is.
We'll send this little trinket to the past.
Everything's ready for our test, General.
November, 1922.
A wonderful moment in history.
I look a little like an Oscar, don't I?
The Tomb of Tutankhamen.
Who is this guy?
We've succeeded.
As I knew we would.
Groomer, pack my bags.
I'm going back in time, before
Shepherd created those Road Rovers.
Once I destroy him,
there'll be no master,
and there'll be only
one trans-dogmafier!
Mine!
Aye, aye, sir.
One last jolt for the road.
It's Parvo's headquarters.
We found him, crew!
Get me out of here, now!
General!
Hold on, General!
Agh! Stupid cat!
Ahh!
No! My General!
Gone!
Forever!
No, Scout.
This cat hasn't done anything wrong.
It's cold and hungry, that's all.
There, there. It's okay, fella.
How about a nice bowl of milk, huh?
See, Scout?
He just wants to be friends.
Wait till the kids see you.
Red alert!
Eliminate the opposition! Now!
Hello, anyone home?
Hey, I know you!
Didn't we meet on a train one time?
You're fluffy!
You're still at it?
I thought you'd be home by now.
What is it with you
and that cat, Shepherd?
You've been bringing that stray
in to work for the past three weeks.
You mean Boots?
What could I say? He adopted me.
Too bad I'm allergic to cats.
Anyway, I'm close to
perfecting the trandogmafier.
Good. That machine's
gonna make us rich.
We've been through this before, Jeffrey.
I'm not interested in profit.
The trans dogma fire is meant
only for the good of the world.
Right, right.
So when do we start testing it?
Soon.
I've been searching the
world for potential candidates.
And several look very promising.
Very promising indeed.
Just remember, it takes more than
dogs to keep this project running.
It takes funding, and lots of it.
And I appreciate all the work you've
done in getting those government grants.
I do what I can.
See you later, Professor.
Dr. Otitis needs to relax, Boats.
Maybe he should get a pet.
I'm telling you, it's a gold mine.
That's right, this transdogmafier
can give dogs awesome abilities.
Sure, I can get the plans to you!
For a price!
Professor Shephard?
He won't know a thing about it.
Proof?
Okay, I'll get your proof.
No one trusts anyone anymore.
Here we go.
Oh no, where's that mutt?
This isn't worth it.
Cat, dog, what's the difference?
Scout, Boots, quiet down.
I'm trying to sleep.
Pipe down!
This won't take long...
Meow!
What did I do!
It's a brand new world.
See? I've built the
transdogmafier from memory.
You'll have an army of cano-mutants.
Are you sure this will work?
Yes, Boots!
I told you I hate that name!
Come up with something better!
Yes, sir, whatever you say.
Now to try it out.
But first, we need a volunteer.
And I know just the dog.
Shepherd's pet.
Scout?
Jeffrey, what are you doing?
Whatever Boots tells me to do.
Boots?
Boots is back?
Meow.
Yep, the cat came back,
new and improved.
But now I'm a man.
No!
Yes.
The dog's ready for
mutation, Boot... eh... sir!
Cano-mutant, huh?
You failed, Otitis.
That dog wasn't transdogmafied.
He's just nuts.
Muzzle him!
Muzzle!
You're needed!
Hi!
Huntie, can I say it this time?
Okay, but say it like you mean it.
Let's muzzle 'em!
And oh man, there goes our G rating.
Blimey!
Mother Russia!
Score is always same
Bad guys zero, muzzle takes all.
Look, it's the Groomer!
Where's she on to?
But Boots, I can build another machine.
You're a complete failure.
It's time to get new help.
Reporting for duty, sir.
Who are you?
They call me the Groomer.
I'm here to serve you, General Parvo.
General Parvo.
I like the sound of that.
Somehow I knew you would.
Here's your first assignment, Groomer.
Dispense with him!
Aye, sir!
Well you need a little off the top!
And the bottom, and all around the edges.
No!
Should I follow him, sir?
I don't think he'll be back.
I like your style, Groomer.
And I like yours general.
But I'm not so sure about him
Listen to this, Shepherd!
It'll be okay, Scout.
It'll be okay.
Satisfied Shepherd?
I just want Scout back.
That dog means a lot to you. Doesn't he?
He is... he's family.
Well, you can have him
back as soon as you hand over
the final blueprints
to the Transdogmifier.
Think it over, Professor.
But don't take too long.
I might change my mind.
I love being human.
What are those?
Oh, Road Rovers, General.
I'll explain later.
You'd better come back with us, Parvo.
You don't belong here.
I don't take orders from dogs.
Gah, we can't lose that mutt!
It's the only bargaining chip we have.
Follow that Rottweiler.
Let's hit the road, Rovers!
This may not be the time
to answer fan mail, Shag.
Uh, It's the past.
No! I'm losing contact with the Rovers.
I have to bring them back to the present.
If I still can.
Wow, cool!
Yes, Shepherd.
I have your dog.
Okay, Parvo.
I'll give you the blueprints.
All I want is Scout.
We'll do the exchange tomorrow night.
Six o'clock.
Your lab.
Don't trust Parvo.
He's going to double-cross you.
Huh?
Welcome back to the present.
You did a great job.
But Parvo got away, Master.
We couldn't stop him.
Yes, but you still saved my life.
We did?
How?
With this.
Master, don't trust Parvo.
He's going to double-cross you.
Love, Shag.
Shag, you got a way with words.
Come on!
We can still make our tea off time.
You're good dogs.
One more passable, Gracie.
You're good, good dogs.