Barkin', scratchin',
frisbee-catchin', presidential pets
That's us!
Change into the canines who
drive souped-up cars and jets
Comin' through!
Tuchus-nippin', toilet-sippin',
Soarin' through the sky
I like it!
Lickin', droolin', quick-refuelin'
who said dogs can't fly
Not me!
Speedin', crashin',
villain-smashin' vehicles explode
Ooh!
Chasing, racing down the road
Road Rovers!
Hunter is a hero
hound, leader of the pack
Huh, cool!
Colleen comes from London
town, watch her feet attack
Exile's from Siberia
with super-frozen sight
That's me
Blitz to chews on posteriors,
his bark's worse than his bite
I'm perfect.
Shag is strong from head to
toe, a coward through and through
Muzzle's stack is gonna
blow, he's short a screw or two
They fight for right both day
and night in every episode
Let's roll!
Now it's time to hit the road
Road Rovers!
I can see the light at
the end of the tunnel.
I'm out.
Now I can see for miles.
I can see everything.
The sky, the mountains, the trees.
And I see you, Oso, brave and strong.
You lead me along the trail,
to the great pyramid of hope.
The pyramid can grant you one wish,
but only if your heart is true.
It's the same vision every morning, Osso,
and you're always in it, leading the way.
I wonder what it means.
Well, come on, we better get home.
Mom's waiting for us.
You know,
if I ever found that pyramid,
I know what I'd wish for.
I'd wish you'd live forever, Oso.
I don't know what I'd
ever do without you.
What is it?
Oso, let's go!
Oso!
The panic on Wall Street continues today
as the Dow Jones Industrials
plummeted more than 500 points
in a frenzied selling session.
The reason for the crash?
A massive influx of gold into
the international marketplace,
sending world economies into a tailspin.
The dollar dropped to a record low today,
as did the German mark,
the Russian ruble,
the Japanese yen, the Swiss
franc, and the British pound.
Well, I can assure you we're
looking into the matter as we speak.
There's a spot of concern here,
what with all the rioting and such.
Tell your people not to panic.
Not panic, ach! This is disaster!
Our entire country is
being bought with this gold.
We have to come up with a solution.
Hey, and lickety split.
Hunter the time has come.
Colleen, you're needed.
Blitz, prepare for battle.
Exile, report to headquarters.
Shag, wake up.
Shag, wake up!
Shag, we have work to do!
No, it can't wait till morning. Now!
Woo hoo! I love this machine!
Hello, Huntie!
I really love this machine.
I feel pretty!
I feel queasy.
I'm with you, Shag. It's lunchtime!
Lunch will have to wait, Rovers.
Right now you have a mission.
Unless the flow of gold is stopped,
a global economic collapse is imminent.
Where's all the bullion
coming from, master?
South America, Hunter.
From a location deep
in the Brazilian rainforest.
Follow the trail of gold, Rovers.
Find out who's controlling
it, then save the world.
Right!
Do you want that done
before or after lunch?
Do it now!
One world saved, coming up!
Let's hit the road, Rovers!
Uh, Master?
Yes?
Just so I'm clear, we can count on
being fed when we get back, right?
Just go.
We're gone!
The Brazilian rainforest, boys and girls.
Trees as far as the eye can see.
I agree, Shag.
So many trees and so little time.
We're right over the
coordinates the master gave us.
Prepare for landing.
But Hunter, there's no runway.
Picky pick.
Have you considered
additional driver's aid?
We don't need additional
drivers and my name's not Ed.
Ah ha ha ha.
Now there's your comedy.
The Amazon, crew.
The world's longest and widest river.
We're on track.
I'm picking up trace amounts of gold dust.
I smell something else too.
Something strong.
It's not me.
I stepped in nothing.
No, it's some kind of animal.
One I've never smelled before.
There are thousands of animals
living here you've never sniffed.
This is a rain forest.
Right.
There are species here that
haven't even been discovered yet.
Like him?
Right.
And of course, there are endangered
species here that face total extinction.
Like us?
Exactly.
Head for the boat!
Something's very strange here.
You mean the mutant piranhas?
Actually I was talking about Shag.
There's your bucket of hell!
Oh, the things you can
learn from Gregory Irons.
Once your tuchus is all
better, I'll come back to bite it.
Don't be weird, boy.
Fire one! Fire two! Fire three!
Hey, nice catch!
Sushi, anyone?
What's that noise?
Shag, answer your phone!
Your phone!
Who's he talking to?
Don't know.
No, really, we're on a mission
in the middle of the Amazon.
Who on Earth is he talking to?
I honestly don't know.
Now is the time for the
blasting of the tuchuses.
It is?
My watch must be slow.
Oops, I did nothing.
Okay, Blitz, hand over the blaster.
No, it's mine!
Sorry, but if you can't use it
correctly then you can't use it at all.
Now hand it over.
No, stop hounding me!
Then quit dogging it!
Get off my tail!
Gents, gents, calm down!
He started it.
Now blister.
Blitz!
Whatever, the point
Hunter's trying to make is...
Watch who you're blasting!
You have a way with words.
Well, it's a gift I was born with.
If she weren't so cute, I'd bite her.
Let's roll Rovers, we
have a mission to finish.
Well, that ought to wrap it up.
I would not have predicted this.
To save our families and our forests,
the monsters must be destroyed.
But I'm not a monster!
Are you a six foot tall
dog man who talks?
Yes.
Close enough.
Destroy him with the others!
Destroy them! Destroy them!
Stop!
These dogs are not the monsters!
They do not smell or sound like the enemy.
Listen to my son!
Yeah! Listen to him! Listen to him!
Little buddy, I believe I speak
for all the Road Rovers when I say...
Whew!
You saved our toast,
man! You're a dude!
Potato! Alright, bro!
Luka is sightless.
But he has seen many things, many visions.
Like what?
I've seen the great pyramid of hope
where one's wish can come true.
Oh, brother.
I've seen all of you
and my visions as well.
I'm so sure.
You're the weird boy.
Hey!
Hehe, Luka, you have 20/20 vision.
Now, if only you could save Oso.
Oso?
My dog.
He has been my eyes for 14 years.
The monsters took him.
They took your dog
Now it's personal.
Let's ride the river Rovers!
Those mutants swam this way.
And the gold level
here is off the meter.
I think we just hit the jackpot
Save it for the concert tour, Shag.
We found the gold pipeline!
And look who's behind it.
GenPar Industries, or more specifically,
General Parvo.
I love the Rainforest
We come here to look
for new biological weapons
Instead we stumble upon the
biggest gold strike of the century.
I'm the luckiest man on Earth.
And the richest.
And soon to be the most powerful.
General, we need to talk.
Is everything alright, Sidney?
You're destroying my discoveries,
melting down priceless
relics for their gold.
It's unconscionable.
It's business, Sidney.
We'll discuss it later.
Let's move on to the issue at hand.
Are we ready for tonight?
Ugh, yes.
The moon will align with
the Pleiades at midnight.
You're positive?
That's what they wrote 2,000 years ago.
The pyramid of hope will awaken and speak
And give to the wisher the wish.
Tonight's the night.
Goodie.
Digit! How go the acquisitions?
We have firm commitments to
buy major sections of Russia,
Morocco, Switzerland, and
the entire state of Montana.
Ah, my people.
But we bought all these
on margin, General.
And payment is due.
So we need to ship the gold now, tonight!
All of it, including the pyramid.
What?
Are you crazy?
General, you can't tear down the pyramid.
It's the eighth wonder of the world.
We need to move quickly, General,
or we'll lose our investments.
The pyramid will be yours to melt, Digit.
No!
After tonight's ceremony.
What's that noise?
Shag, answer your phone!
The phone!
Who keeps calling him?
I don't know.
Road Rovers!
Oh hi. Hehe.
It's for you.
Finish them off, Groomer!
With extreme prejudice, sir.
This way!
It's supper time, my little fishies!
Make the nice doggies all gone!
So where are the rovers?
Being digested, sir.
Stop making me laugh, Groomer!
Oh sorry sir.
Ah yeah!
Ta-da!
Oso?
Luka sent us.
He misses you.
So, let's get you home.
Come on comrades, start rushing!
Oso, wait man,
that's the wrong way out.
Come back!
Time she has come.
I agree.
Let's muzzel them.
Ох, Мазл. (Oh, Muzzle.)
I made thoughts my cookies were crumbling.
I too am feeling a pinch, woozy.
Wow!
Abso-bloomin'-lutely awesome!
In a moment we'll have it all.
General, don't destroy
everything I've worked for.
When I agreed to dig here you
promised it would all be preserved.
Sydney, I lied.
Now read this to me one last
time or I'll feed you to the piranhas.
L'am paka shakama.
The light will shine on
one whose heart is true,
And one wish will be granted.
What are you going to wish for, General?
Guess.
Complete world domination?
Oh, right you are.
This is it.
Oso.
One wish is given to the
one whose heart is true.
Back to the hover rover!
It serves you right.
We're ruined, man.
Lozenge?
Nah.
Then the light shined down on Oso.
And he made his wish.
To shut down Parvo's
operation for Good-ski?
No. Oso wished for something else.
He wished for me to have eyesight.
I can see you Oso,
for the very first time.
You are more beautiful
than I had ever imagined.
You've taken care of me all these years.
Now it's my turn to take care of you.
Deep inside every dog is a Road Rover.
Good job, Rovers.
The world financial markets
have stabilized, thanks to you.
What's that noise?
Shag, answer your phone!
Who is he talking to all the time?
Well, apparently the caterers.
It's lunchtime!