Barkin', scratchin',
frisbee-catchin', presidential pets
That's us!
Change into the canines who
drive souped-up cars and jets
Comin' through!
Tuchus-nippin', toilet-sippin',
Soarin' through the sky
I like it!
Lickin', droolin', quick-refuelin'
who said dogs can't fly
Not me!
Speedin', crashin',
villain-smashin' vehicles explode
Ooh!
Chasing, racing down the road
Road Rovers!
Hunter is a hero
hound, leader of the pack
Huh, cool!
Colleen comes from London
town, watch her feet attack
Exile's from Siberia
with super-frozen sight
That's me
Blitz to chews on posteriors,
his bark's worse than his bite
I'm perfect.
Shag is strong from head to
toe, a coward through and through
Muzzle's stack is gonna
blow, he's short a screw or two
They fight for right both day
and night in every episode
Let's roll!
Now it's time to hit the road
Road Rovers!
Captain Zachary Storm, please rise.
You have been found guilty of
treason against the United States.
The justice system is a conspiracy.
You have no authority over me.
I hereby sentence you to federal prison
for life with no possibility of parole.
This is just a minor setback.
Bailiff, take him away.
No, not me.
Nooooo!
As UFO sightings continue,
today at Camp David, the President
and other world leaders have
gathered to review the crisis.
According to our data, there's
no clear pattern to these sightings.
Reminds me a bit of those
mysterious crop circles we have,
except they don't go
around disintegrating people.
It's okay, Hunter.
It's okay.
Now as of this morning, NATO
forces have been put on full alert.
Mr. President, Germany's
military is standing by.
You can count on us.
Her Majesty's armed forces
are ready to assist in any way.
Russia's Ministry of Defense
is prepared to crush any threat.
Well, if we're unable to remain neutral,
then the Swiss guards will be ready.
Good.
At tomorrow's press
conference, we'll announce
the formation of a planetary
peacekeeping alliance.
I suggest that we all
get a chunky, lunky burger,
maybe a large fry and a malt,
and then sack out.
What do you say?
Hey, even you boy.
Keep rolling.
What is it?
You'd better stay back, Mr. President.
We'll take care of this.
Sir, I suggest you
and the others evacuate.
No. We need to put a
stop to this once and for all.
Hillary?
Oh, she's not here.
No, stay, Hunter.
I'll be fine.
I do not have a good feeling about this.
It's okay, Hunter.
What do they want, sir?
Unconditional surrender.
We've been waiting over five
hours for the press conference to begin,
and there is still no word
from the world leaders on how
they plan to respond to
last night's alien ultimatum.
Ha!
You've gone mad!
I have proof that
England is covertly involved
with these aliens and
a grab for world power.
You dare accuse my country?
Your country's behind this.
This is an insidious
British-American co-venture.
Nein, it is Swiss
spying for world domination.
Боже мой! (My god!)
All of you are conspiring to
overthrow my government.
If you persist with these accusations,
I will be forced to
declare war on all of you.
Then war it is.
Rovers, this is a red alert.
It's time to save the world.
Rovers, we're on the brink of a
disaster that could destroy the planet.
The leaders of the world are talking war.
Everyone should listen to my owner.
He's the only one making sense.
Да (yeah), nonsense.
Watch your tongue, snowball.
You should talk, weird boy.
I'm going to bite you so hard.
Get off my tail.
Quit hounding me.
Stop bickering.
We're trying to stop a
war, not start another one.
Rovers, this crisis
is related to that UFO.
I want you to track it down.
Let's hit the skies.
Satellite indicates UFO
last spotted near Great Lakes.
What do these aliens want?
They may be after our planet
or maybe they're after our brains.
Oof, even mine?
Sure, it's the little things that count.
Or they might be after our food.
Shag says now it's personal.
Wow!
Close encounter of the worst kind.
Colleen, I need your help.
Everyone else, abandon ship.
Whatever happened to
women and children first?
Another cliche bites the dust.
Are you sure you know
how that pump works, Hunter?
Nope, but it's worth a try.
And if it doesn't work?
How long can you hold your breath?
Not long enough.
You never learned how to doggy paddle?
What a shame for both of us.
Lucky for us, comrade, we have chutes.
I didn't say it was good lucky for us.
Easy Muzzle, I give bad guys big chill.
That will learn them.
Oops.
They are fast learners.
Move along.
Hey, stop shoving.
Look what the cat dragged in.
Don't start with me.
I'm feeling a tad cranky.
Well, well.
It seems the planet Earth
has truly gone to the dogs.
Put the prisoners through a neural brain
scrambler to ensure their loyalty to me.
Just like the leaders
of their little world.
Please, Mr. Alien, sir, I beg
of you, don't scramble my brain.
It's so teeny tiny, it wouldn't
even make a decent omelet.
Please.
Engage that ship
and this time I'll obliterate it.
Boy, I'm glad that pump worked.
I'll say.
Faster, Huntie Wuntie.
They are mine.
Commander, sensors
are picking up something new.
I would not have predicted this.
How's it wagging, Space Rovers?
All systems go, Hunter.
Engaging laser launchers.
Come again?
Initiating retrieval maneuvers.
Hey, you're from
another country, aren't you?
Ready, Huntie?
You bet. Catch!
We need reinforcements.
What we are about to do
should not happen to a dog.
It won't. It'll happen to them.
Muzzle 'em!
Cold War was never like this.
I'm feeling a little dyspepsia.
Yo, monkey boy.
Leaving the party already?
Who do they send to stop me?
Not the FBI. Not the CIA.
They send mutts! A grave tactical error.
Storm!
But you're dead.
You're a dead alien, ghost, zombie thingy.
That's what I wanted everyone to think.
He wasn't vaporized after all.
It was special effects.
Oh, cool! Did ILM do 'em?
That must have cost.
A fortune
I'm glad you liked the
illusion, but the show's over.
You see, the captain is going
down with the ship, and so are you.
The ship will
self-destruct in 30 seconds.
Yet another unexpected twist. Bummer.
All tushies bitten and accounted for.
20 seconds to blast off.
20, 19, 18, 17, 16...
15, 14, 13, 12, 11, 10...
Hurry, Exile. If we don't
warp out of here now, we're toast.
Do you like your
toast with jam or honey?
Eh... jam. And don't call me honey.
5...
4, 3, 2, 1...
What about all of Storm's mercenaries?
They'll be picked up by the Navy.
To the power of the pack!
Now, where were we?
Captain Zachary Storm,
once again you've been found guilty
of treason against the United States.
I sentence you to
federal prison for a double
life sentence with no
possibility of parole.
Dream on, judge.
I guarantee you I'll eclipse
everything I've ever done before.
And the whole world will know
the Storm can never be stopped.
Never!
Couldn't happen to a nicer maniac.
And again, he might
not be at the top of the list.
I love you most.
We have peace on Earth, for a
while at least, thanks to you rovers.
Cool! This calls for a group hug!
Where in the Road Rover
manual does it say we have to do this?
The footnote on page 227.
Oh, fine print gets me every time.
Finally, the nightmare is over.
Now if we could just calm
things down in Bosnia.
Sweet dreams, Shag.
Enough biting, Blitz. It's time for bed.
999, 1000. There, all done.
Now it's off to bed, dear.
We'll play some more tomorrow, Hunter.
Right now, all I wanna do is
get over that whitewater thingy.
Get some sleep.
They'll learn. The hard way.
Not even prison bars can stop
me from controlling the world.
Excuse me? What do you mean?
Just watch the moon, buddy boy.
Yeah, it's all happening now.
I don't understand.
When the lunar eclipse is
at its apex, the war will begin.
But how?
I planted a post-hypnotic suggestion
in the minds of the world's leaders.
Oh, no.
And they thought they
could stop me. Hehe...
Stand by for verification codes.
But Mr. President, these codes authorize
the immediate activation of our missiles.
Correct, General. Now do it.
Prepare for launching.
You heard me correctly.
We're not neutral anymore.
Complete obliteration.
The time is at hand.
Hunter, wake up.
Colleen, you too.
Blitz.
Shag.
Dream about hydrants
some other night, Shag.
Exile, this is a full Road Rover alert.
The world leaders are
about to set off a full-scale war.
You need to stop them
before the eclipse is complete.
No, Hunter!
There's no time to
transdogmafy into Road Rovers.
You've got to do it on your own.
There's no other way.
Receiving emergency
message for strategic missile launch.
Begin verification codes.
Bravo, Echo, Tango.
Hey, cut it out, Hunter.
What was that, sir?
Hey!
Avon, Piccadilly, Abbey.
Colleen, what's wrong with you?
This won't do at all.
Разный, звенья, собака.
Exile, you will be sent
back to Siberia for this.
Zurich, Geneva, Lucerne.
Yep, doggy breath.
Doggy breath? I'm afraid
that's not part of the code, sir.
Sieben, Reich, Eis, Tindern.
Ah, Blitz! Mein heilig! (My god!)
Hunter, knock it off.
Whoa!
We need the final code for
the launch if we're to proceed, sir.
Launch? What am I doing?
Abort! Cancel launch immediately!
Heavens, abort the launch.
Боже мой! (My god!) stop missiles now!
We're neutral again.
Halt den Blitzkrieg! (Stop the strike!)
I don't fully understand
what happened last night, Hunter,
but hoo-wee, I think you saved
the world from total destruction.
You're a genuine hero.
If it wasn't for you, Colleen, I shudder
to think what might have happened.
You are true comrade, Exile.
Dankeschön (thanks), Blitz. I think.
Eat up, Shag. You deserve it.
Deep inside every dog is a road rover.
You're good, good dogs.
I'll be back! You'll see!
What doesn't kill me makes me stronger!
Besides, old soldiers never die.
They keep coming back for more.
Excuse me.
Could you please keep it down?
We're in the middle of a meeting.
Now, Spider, you'll control Russia.
Flee, China is yours.
And Cockroach, you can have Iran.
You can't split up the world.
It's mine to rule! Mine!
You can't rule the world.
You're not a bug.
You're not going to rule, are you?
No, it is I who shall
rule the world, yes.
You can't! You can't! It's mine!
No! No, no, no, no!