Barkin', scratchin',
frisbee-catchin', presidential pets
That's us!
Change into the canines who
drive souped-up cars and jets
Comin' through!
Tuchus-nippin', toilet-sippin',
Soarin' through the sky
I like it!
Lickin', droolin', quick-refuelin'
who said dogs can't fly
Not me!
Speedin', crashin',
villain-smashin' vehicles explode
Ooh!
Chasing, racing down the road
Road Rovers!
Hunter is a hero
hound, leader of the pack
Huh, cool!
Colleen comes from London
town, watch her feet attack
Exile's from Siberia
with super-frozen sight
That's me
Blitz to chews on posteriors,
his bark's worse than his bite
I'm perfect.
Shag is strong from head to
toe, a coward through and through
Muzzle's stack is gonna
blow, he's short a screw or two
They fight for right both day
and night in every episode
Let's roll!
Now it's time to hit the road
Road Rovers!
So I tell the shlemeel,
Robin, I say "back off, pal!"
I'm the king of radio.
No one can touch me.
What do you think of that?
I mean, this guy is really annoying, Robin.
He's more annoying than those French.
I wish he'd retreat like the
French during World War II.
Anyway, this guy's driving me crazier
than Jackie at renegotiation time.
No kidding.
I don't care if he is the
head of the FCC, Robin.
Morning, Colleen.
Morning, Huntie Wuntie.
Morning, pretty girl doggy.
Well, hello, and welcome
to Road Rover Headquarters.
You must be one of the new cadets.
Glad to have you aboard.
No, you know me.
I'm Blitz.
No, no, no. We like
to give all our new cadets nicknames,
you know, funny nicknames
that make us laugh.
Let's see.
What can we call you...
Oh, here's one.
How about Mr. Chubby Cheeks?
What?
From now on, your name is
Mr. Chester Chubby Cheeks.
Okay, don't call me that.
Or maybe just Chubbikins for short.
That's it. I've had it
with your little name game.
Let the biting begin.
Sorry.
Seems the name Chubbikins
has already been taken.
So why don't we call you Mr. Puffy Lips?
Yeah. It works for me.
Shag, you've done it again.
Another gourmet delight.
I couldn't agree more.
Hunter, you are a road rover now.
You don't have to eat
from bowl on floor anymore.
Yeah, I know, but some habits die hard.
Open the door.
What's going on?
Shag is hogging the bathroom, again.
Hey, hurry it up, Shag.
We all have to use it.
Leave some for us, will you?
Gather round, Rovers.
You have a busy day ahead.
Here's your schedule.
Free the hostages, attend
the peace treaty signing,
And track down this
unidentified alien spacecraft.
Sure thing, Master.
But what do we do after lunch?
Ha!
Now there's your comedy.
Let's move out, Rovers.
Now hold it right there.
Why is Hunter in charge all the time?
What about me?
How come you're always the leader?
Well, for one thing, I'm smarter than you.
No, you're not.
Yeah, I am.
Prove it!
Okay, now look over there.
What?
Now look over there.
Look over there.
What?
Now look over there.
Look over there.
What?
Now look over there.
Now this could go on forever.
Crew buckle up!
Let's hit the road, Rovers.
When do I get to drive?
As soon as my license gets revoked.
Your pilot's license?
No, my dog license.
You know, I think we've done this joke.
That's true.
We're recycling.
Shag, quit hogging up room of relief!
What are you working on, Hunter?
A missing dog case.
You know, just trying to update the files.
I'm an expert on missing dogs.
Let me see.
Hey, don't mess with my stuff, okay?
It's private.
Wow, ho-ho-ho.
Achtung! Ach! (Watch out! Oh!)
Who's the babe?
She's not a babe, okay?
So back off.
Ooh, touchy, touchy, Mr. Touchy.
Just mind your own business, puffy lips.
Yeah, what do you know?
Hunter has girlfriend.
Ha ha, ha ha ha ha ha ha.
You remind me of polar bear I once knew.
His name was Binky.
He smelled like Staten
Island garbage scout.
Ah, that is much better.
Thank you very much.
We need someone to draw their fire.
Hey, don't look at me.
I'm just here temping while
the regular girl's on vacation.
If we can sneak in behind that guard shack,
we might be able to free the hostages.
What do you think?
Well, we could try your plan,
or we might try a plan that actually works.
Yeah, tough choice.
Total toss-up.
Okay, Rovers, let's roll.
I could have been born a cat, but no.
I give you cold shoulder and
cold head, cold back, cold tushy.
Leave the tushies to me
and let the biting begin.
We're friends, and we're
getting you out of here.
We'd like to welcome the hostages
back home, where they belong.
Job well done, Rovers.
Thanks, Master.
Oh, and by the way,
remember that alien ship we
were supposed to track down?
Yes?
Looks like it beat us to the punch.
Ha. I would not have predicted this.
But this is how it's all going to end.
No, but it's already 12 noon.
Time sure flies when you're having fun.
Who are these jokers?
I don't know, but they're screwing
up our very busy schedule.
Let's lose them.
Roger.
Nice work, Colleen.
But don't call me Roger.
What's next on the agenda?
Next is perhaps our most
important mission of the day.
Lunchtime!
Yeah, we need 12 jumbos with
the works, 6 fries, 5 root beers and...
Hey, Blitz, what do you want to drink?
Do they have peppermint milkshakes?
Oh yeah,
they got a big vat of those out back.
Make that six root beers.
Peppermint milkshakes.
Thanks!
Woah
Diggity-dank wheels!
Road Rovers, not too dull.
Uh-huh.
Only one problem.
What's that?
They paid with old tennis balls.
Spew?
Spew.
Delicious!
What is it they are calling the meat
tube inside the small bread loaf?
Oh, that's the great
American meal, the hot dog.
Hot dog?
Why, for is it named like this?
No one really knows.
Oh, no, I am eating one of my dog comrades.
I am cannibal boy.
No, it's not made from dog.
Then why call it hot dog?
Because it's served warm
and shaped like a dachshund.
Ah, it's wiener dog friend.
Now I am doing the choking.
Here, let me Heimlich you.
Don't even think about it.
Fill her up with premium.
That is the most disgusting
men's room I've ever been in.
Me first.
Gangway!
On behalf of the Rovers,
I just want to thank you.
Oh, boy.
So, Hunter, what's with
the dog in the picture?
Eh, it's a long story, Exile.
It's a long flight.
She's beautiful, isn't she?
Да. (Yes.)
I finally tracked her down.
It took quite a while.
Where does she live?
Wyoming, out in the middle of nowhere.
You should go see her.
Yeah, how?
We're busy all the time at
state functions, on missions.
You must make time for the
important things, comrade.
Exile, what are you doing?
What's going on?
We're making a brief stop in Wyoming.
Heh.
Well, what are you waiting for?
Go down and see her.
I don't know what to say.
You'll figure it out.
Just go.
But what about the peace treaty signing?
We'll handle it.
We'll come back to pick you up in an hour.
Are you sure?
Just go.
Okay, I won't be long.
Yeah, right.
I've heard that story before.
So long, Huntie.
Stay calm. It's okay.
It's okay, really.
Here, smell. See?
It's just me.
Yeah, it's just me.
It's okay. It's okay.
That's right.
It's good to see you too, Mama.
And it's good to be home.
That treaty signing at the U.N.
went better than I expected.
I just wish Blitz hadn't
bitten Sam Donalds.
Hey, give me that.
Oh, my.
I had no choice.
His toupee attacked me.
It's getting late.
We'd better go pick up Hunter.
I'm afraid that may be impossible.
Yet another unexpected twist.
Bummer.
State your name.
Blitz.
And what were you
before you were a Road Rover?
Well, I was a guard dog.
I would guard the auto yard all night.
And if the burglars came by,
I would bark at them.
You know, I would go, "Woof,
woof," and say,
"Go away! Get away from here."
You are bothering me.
"And if they didn't leave, I would
show the fangs like this, okay?
And that is when the biting would begin.
I enjoy biting the tushie.
It's soft and squishy.
And I like to go like this.
This is good exercise for the gums,
And it makes the peoples
run away really fast.
I've actually kept a record
of all the tushies I've bitten.
If I make it to a thousand,
I get a new flea collar.
That is my goal.
Would you ever divulge
the secrets of the road rovers?
Never.
And if you were tortured?
Exactly, what would you like to know?
Hey, what's the blooming idea?
Who are you blokes?
What do you want with us?
We'll ask the questions, Rover.
Now, tell us everything.
Who are you?
Well, there's not much to tell, really.
I'm Colleen.
Hello.
I was born at an early age went to
obedience school, and flunked paper training.
So, watch your step.
My passions include chasing the mailman,
squeaky toys shaped like bananas,
and large sizzling shanks of fatty pork.
Yummy.
Would you like to know more?
No, that's plenty.
Good. Then I can go.
I'll take that as a probable no.
State your name.
Your name.
What is your name?
Oh, never mind. Next!
Tell us about the inner
workings of the road rovers.
What did he say?
He says he wants his lawyer.
Stop stalling and tell
us your secrets. Now!
Well, there you have it.
A what?
Shag's secret recipe for Kung Pao Chicken.
Mix with toilet water, serves ten.
Okay, rovers.
The game is over.
Parvo!
And the Groomer!
You've had your fun.
Now it's time for us to have ours.
So anyway, I searched
through all the computer files,
and I finally followed the records
back here to you, Mom.
I guess that's why they named me Hunter.
No, I can't stay.
I'm a Road Rover now. I'm part of a team.
And it looks like they need me.
I gotta go.
Yes, I promise I'll be careful.
And I love you too, Mom.
I know you're scared, but just keep calm.
Before we lower you into the molten
hot rocks, Rovers,
any last requests?
Yes, I have one.
Would you make me a nice,
refreshing peppermint milkshake?
Eww. Request denied.
Let's get this over with.
Lower away!
Peppermint milkshake.
I like minty things, so sue me.
This is a happy day.
Aye, that is, sir.
Hello. What have we here?
Let's see what this baby can do.
Beware of dogs.
No.
Let's muzzle 'em.
No!
I am thankin' goodness you arrived
in nick-of-time-ski, comrade Hunter.
Hey, I'm just sorry I
wasn't there sooner, bro.
So all right, already tell us what
happened with your girlfriend.
What girlfriend?
That girl dog back on the farm.
Oh, that's not my girlfriend.
That's my mother.
Your mom?
Yeah, I hadn't seen her
since I was eight weeks old.
I had a heck of a time tracking her down.
Who'd you think it was?
Oh, well, I...
She thought you
had a new girlfriend,
and you know, that
you were dumping her,
and she was all jealous
and upset, and...
Sorry, that was uncalled for on my part.
You okay, Blitz?
My name is Mr. Puffy Lips, but
you can call me an ambulance.
Let's take it home, Rovers.
Welcome back, Rovers.
You know, Blitz, this peppermint
milkshake is pretty good-ski.
Told you so.
I guess you're not such
a weird boy after all.
You really mean that?
No. I'm just making conversation.
You're way weird boy.
Oh.
So, Huntie?
Yeah?
There's a moon out tonight.
Huh, cool.
So, do you want to go
for a walk on the beach?
Do I? You bet!
This is not exactly what I had in mind.
You've done a great job today, Rovers.
You're good dogs.
Shag, open the door-ski, will you?
A little disgusting some of the time,
but basically, you're good, good dogs.